gigafact: hello
loopylol: sup sup
gigafact: you look wet
TooManyBytes: monkaS hopefully the teacher forgot the test
michelfugain69: first
michelfugain69: im ur biggest fan
gtnftw: GEORGE
thes1nbad: hiii
michelfugain69: PogChamp
EhGuyInCanada: Is there going to be a test,
Aqualyn: NotLikeThis
TowlieGotHigh: YEP Test
danizx2: hey
alexmchugh: sup
EhGuyInCanada: Test time?
lambdaman0f: everybody done their homework?
norflin221: hello
gtnftw: You don't dry your hair when done?
angie_exe: heyyy
ay420notbannedlmao: link to test
marschr: wheres the feeling bro
loduerik: @georgehotz hEY u got any advice for a 18 year old?
lesnerdav: yooooo
B1_Renekton: test?
32bitrobo: Suh dude
Joooooooooonas: you got the test prof ?
Joooooooooonas: Kappa
JohnnyThe_Hobo: more cameras
ilzh: hello
gtnftw: @loduerik my advice is to git gud LUL
livehoc: @georgehotz I have a referall link for Google Foobar coding challenge, let me know if you want it
bipinoli: what's with that FSM?
TowlieGotHigh: LEAKED LUL
ay420notbannedlmao: did you get any of those no repaymen loans for your biz?
yanhaoli: What’s up!
evvirtanen: let's go
gtnftw: @bipinoli it's part of the busy beaver thing
marschr: LOOOOL
JohnnyThe_Hobo: lets gooo
StealerSlain: who've read the thing here LUL?
Zinx153: Hi
bipinoli: oo thanks @gtnftw
marschr: wth is clubhouse?
B1_Renekton: ??
diddyp1_LiiD: quiz time!
anguscupcake: Oh hell yea
solitaryyy: wasn't joking about the test lol
ericvaneri9k: heyyyyy got that sheep hair
JohnnyThe_Hobo: if(answer = no)
abeltefera01: i'm a sub
jamieemb_: Hiya George
annestion41: ?????????
solitaryyy: I finally think you're serious about the university - actually wrote a test for the stream
ay420notbannedlmao: link to the camwhore vids?
axlebear: Only fans?
anguscupcake: need onlyfans
ericvaneri9k: geoge whats your morning go to drink ? @georgehotz
solitaryyy: non-nude PogChamp
SanJacobs: Step 1: Stream more than once a year
axlebear: I gotta see that fat hog
sw1jari: tough luck george
PlomLo12: LULW
aaddrr: link_
Sleeper009: Is this Tesla's business model?
aaddrr: link?
solitaryyy: LOL
pxlluu: hello lirikHS
loopylol: LUL
B1_Renekton: LULW
ay420notbannedlmao: KEKW
marschr: looool
echotaco: You can increase earnings by 20% if you apply for partnership ;) @georgehotz
bipinoli: SeemsGood
theknip: @georgehotz where is my stream entrance test?
sw1jari: PogChamp
TowlieGotHigh: Sure Kappa
solitaryyy: LUL
annestion41: PogChamp full time streamer
21_savior: lmao
Dautlog: I bet George would love TTS spam Kappa
ericvaneri9k: damn why did you move to Ny
Hypheus_: bits twitch takes the money when people buy them so you get 100% of the bits people use
echotaco: You can negotiate a 3.5/5 split instead of the usual 2.5/5 @georgehotz
EhGuyInCanada: What are you going to do to people who don’t pass the test?
Faceless_Bard: title said rumoured Kappa
TowlieGotHigh: @EhGuyInCanada Ban us KEKW
patrickgekko: patrickgekko subscribed at Tier 1.
loopylol: to the shadow realm
myaocat: hello how you doing
sw1jari: cam websites take a lot and you don't get a higher cut if you're high in the rankings
stanislav_ts: what's happening right now?
sw1jari: from what i've heard
Vjasal: I just joined, how do i start the test?
ay420notbannedlmao: bro do the test quick i have a tinder date in 20
B1_Renekton: logtiech webcams are good
ericvaneri9k: good quality camera no need tp change
Faceless_Bard: its the dslr/mirrorless era , not webcam DansGame
21_savior: long $LOGI
Joooooooooonas: TOS
Joooooooooonas: Dude
loopylol: TOS
Joooooooooonas: TOS
annestion41: Kreygasm
HurricaneFP: where's the test ?
alexmchugh: TOS TOS TOS
Hypheus_: monkaS
Aqualyn: LUL
Vjasal: xsplit DansGame
solitaryyy: xd
EhGuyInCanada: Q&A at the end of the stream again?
ay420notbannedlmao: thats a man
Sunce_: I think u are allowed asmongold did it and disguised toast did videos about their twitch earnings sachio1Hmm @georgehotz
g_gWillis: monkaS
stanstill: what am i seeing
21_savior: partner btw LuL
B1_Renekton: what about the wall next to you?
SanJacobs: Webcam is so last decade
bravech: George gonna get banned
Joooooooooonas: yes it is
blasio115: monkaS
sw1jari: that's fine
B1_Renekton: it is voilation
stanstill: THIS IS TWITCH
AwaisDota: LUL
loopylol: theyve banned for less LUL
Sleeper009: Reported Kappa
Faceless_Bard: no nipples were shown , we are safe
blasio115: LUL
Sunce_: LUL
chetta: we aint snitchin, NOBODY SNITCH
Hypheus_: LUL
i_Memberino: its not a violation chat chill
Kubissus: LUL
TowlieGotHigh: TRUE LUL
TheRealMast3r: LUL
Sunce_: oh no no LUL
reesync: nmpKEK
chetta: Nobody here is gonna snitch, we good!
solitaryyy: LOL
sw1jari: idk maybe if you seek it out i tis
Joooooooooonas: it is
aaddrr: TRUE LULW
loopylol: well find out tomorrow
loopylol: LMAO
Sunce_: monkaS
thes1nbad: LUL LUL LU L LUL LUL LUL
SanJacobs: They've banned for WAY LESS
aaddrr: WATTCH OUT MAN HAHAHA
Joooooooooonas: no underwear allowed on twitch
SanJacobs: Alinnity is immune!
g_gWillis: hasPause
ay420notbannedlmao: just dont talk about race crime stats and youre good
Kubissus: @Joooooooooonas so naked only?
bakuldada: will u be doing a workout stream someday
cybergenik: Why are you so wet?
Aehoard: LUL Youre cute and ignorant
daxyxy98: Tom Cross LUL
Sunce_: Kreygasm
Moscowwbish: george HOTz Kreygasm
Den_dp: georgehots
ericvaneri9k: dont you use an external monitor rn ?
sw1jari: tomc00m
Aqualyn: SabaPing
solitaryyy: Take off your bra George
loopylol: georges black tight tshirt Kreygasm
Faceless_Bard: this blogpost knows
K0enich: LuvPeekL
Hypheus_: Kreygasm
Sleeper009: Kreygasm
bubblesnot: When is the quiz?
reesync: Kreygasm no bra
sw1jari: george in freedom shirt Kreygasm
TurboWalrusTickler: Excuse me?
astrocraft23: hi
Sunce_: Kreygasm I Lost
ay420notbannedlmao: sex change this year?
neilsweb: Is this the busy beaver paper?
SanJacobs: She been in DA GAME
loopylol: poppin
TekniqueTrading: 30k subs!
stanstill: WHY ARE YOU SO SWEATY
biniar_: Are you verified on Instagram?
gigafact: followers
bakuldada: get on more podcasts
gtnftw: he meant followers I think
alexmchugh: followers prob
TekniqueTrading: 30k subs thats a huge dub
alexmchugh: i think he means followers
Rohitbokade94: show your curves
TekniqueTrading: yee I know what he meant
B1_Renekton: 50k a month holy mothern of god
ericvaneri9k: im rich im hood i look good
eldac_kno: quality content
Sunce_: We need gachi emotes LUL
gtnftw: 420
Vjasal: if i give you money will something vibrate?
i_Memberino: 419
ericvaneri9k: sory sory lol
anguscupcake: bruh... I’m going female
plotzera: 420 LUL
echotaco: The largest streamer in this category routinely has 15k+ viewers doing comparatively a lot more simple things, so there's a lot more room for growth @georgehotz
Faceless_Bard: @georgehotz do you get emails from fanclub ?
bakuldada: get on austin datingg show or heyitsjoe show with thousands of viewers for exposure
marschr: 439 rn
loopylol: did you work on anything off stream
movsdk: DatSheffy
TekniqueTrading: @echotaco who is that
ay420notbannedlmao: implying ur getting to 500
leander_ms: Dude you are wet and this stream is not yet sub only so we still have time for shitposting guye
alexmchugh: if i give u money will tabs turn into spaces?
bubblesnot: I am nervous about the test teacher
echotaco: Michael Reeves @TekniqueTrading
TowlieGotHigh: @georgehotz Get a 2nd monitor so u can read twitch chat easier and engage with community :)
thetimetraveler253: George how was your date?
TekniqueTrading: @echotaco tyty
eldac_kno: play chess with moistkritical
Sunce_: George sachio1L
bakuldada: get on some dating shows to get exposure
cutza: to grow you need to deploy bots that day "subscribe and I'll subscribe back"
bubblesnot: Is that clean hair or greasy hair?
gigafact: other twitch streamers are boring
stanstill: THIS IS AN EXCUSE TO GET A DATE WITHA CAMGIRL
Faceless_Bard: fixing your hair would be first
daxyxy98: Pair Programming Session LUL
Vjasal: wet Kreygasm
Sunce_: esfandL your face is enough <3
21_savior: someone donate him a towel
blasio115: LUL
TheRealMast3r: Your kitchen is visually attractive
ay420notbannedlmao: nice hair girl
sw1jari: george in freedom shirt is visually appealing Kreygasm
stanstill: why so sweaty
neilsweb: Did you google "how to become a cam girl?"
annestion41: WTFF
ericvaneri9k: i think maybe youll need to change the camera angel look like we all under you looking up your nose
Aqualyn: Kreygasm
solitaryyy: drunk naked george stream
solitaryyy: 10/10
Sunce_: LUL
Faceless_Bard: drunk streams
loopylol: take nots boys
gtnftw: I like the way she thinks LULW
Avelansh: naked cooking streams
cybergenik: lol
burgerlove_: hell yeah, naked george making mac and cheese
bubblesnot: These suggestions are cringe
bakuldada: nerdy workout and dance stream
JohnnyThe_Hobo: :(
Sunce_: D:
SanJacobs: drunk naked mac and cheese stream Pog
axlebear: Finally some real content ideas
CaptainMoistNuclear: emotional support in the form of naked mac n cheese
thearthtyagi: yo
blasio115: D:
nednassim: Sir , I like your madness bro
marschr: emo stream was yesterday already
loopylol: 500 wooo
NatePh_07: LUL
bojosos: 500
krystalgamer: ayyy
Sunce_: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
B1_Renekton: 500
thetimetraveler253: Do you prefer dating girls in CS?
spindriftur: Hi
ay420notbannedlmao: we did it reddit
phrixus_bro: hyperloyal whales, welcome
georgehotz: https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
loopylol: george cooking stream PogChamp
REDMX96: the man himself
TowlieGotHigh: @georgehotz Get a 2nd monitor BabyRage it will help u alot
damooooooooooh: yo George what's up with hammer
loopylol: yesssir
marschr: he drank from the pink can again
echotaco: https://www.twitchmetrics.net/ and https://socialblade.com/ for some data ;) @georgehotz
Faceless_Bard: your instagram is dead though
ay420notbannedlmao: instagram KEKW
krystalgamer: i love how you have your stream open in the back, creating the infinite loop
REDMX96: Tinder?
Aqualyn: :D
annestion41: 1m2019 com
Sunce_: Using us D: @georgehotz
blasio115: Kappa
B1_Renekton: instagram owned by facebook cmon
TheRealMast3r: LUL
biniar_: but not verified on Instagram
goobygoobler: amiloLul
bojosos: give us the test
SnakeOneMLG: did he break up with Alex :o
eldac_kno: play chess with GM Hikaru or Moist Critical
ay420notbannedlmao: test
axlebear: spin around so we can see what we’re working with
ericvaneri9k: we want cooking streams i forgot how to cook i need your recepices
movsdk: you have a real quality neural network here LUL LUL
alexmchugh: yeah how do u reconcile using instagram as a facebook product?
solitaryyy: 4k lolz
zennydmt: where do you live?
cybergenik: SeemsGood Instagram DMs
Aqualyn: holy
momolive: 4 grand wtf
REDMX96: damn son
bubblesnot: Do you get your dates from linkedin?
MrSolo734: holy
Silver5005: LOL
ay420notbannedlmao: cheap
goobygoobler: jesus
gtnftw: that's insane rent
Vjasal: @georgehotz what research paper are you reading rn?
ericvaneri9k: @zennydmt NY
THENEXTMOSES: THENEXTMOSES subscribed with Twitch Prime.
fishpizza: Manhattan money
BigBurrito_09: LUL
TekniqueTrading: 4k LUL
leiterLAB: 4K LUL
rdrgcnt: man, you gotta make wooden figures amd br humble
session_variable: how we doing boys
daxyxy98: quick 40x
NatePh_07: one stream a day is not enough LUL
zennydmt: georgehotz lives in NY?
thetimetraveler253: I'm making $0 by watching your streams. I need to increase me revenue.
momolive: 4k where do you live tho?
BigBurrito_09: $100 income $4k rent LUL
TekniqueTrading: what hapopend to "I bought a van" @georgehotz
myaocat: @thetimetraveler253 *my
Aqualyn: 🐋
Sunce_: esfandM 💰 esfandM 💰 esfandM 💰
krystalgamer: it was not ME
Digital_donger: doesn't even know the username LUL
Silver5005: bars
Den_dp: he's in header, just look
zennydmt: do you like NY Pizza?
gtnftw: I am one of the whale's offspring. My sub was purchased by whale
CJslider14: CJslider14 subscribed at Tier 1.
ericvaneri9k: tea or coffee ? @georgehotz
goobygoobler: sponsored by that guy
B1_Renekton: @georgehotz were you actually botom 5 in your class?
Joooooooooonas: Thats gifted subs dude
ay420notbannedlmao: test test
gtnftw: 5 gifted subs from John
session_variable: ooohhh i should make some coffee
neilsweb: neilsweb subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Aqualyn: Already a pro strimer PogChamp
gigafact: hype train wow
myaocat: SCAM TRAIN PogU
echotaco: Download streamlabs OBS so you can set subscriber alerts @georgehotz
blasio115: scam train PogChamp
Sunce_: Hype train PogChamp
TowlieGotHigh: SCAM TRAIN POGGERS
21_savior: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
cefaloclever: I saw you on twich fails compilation, you are popping
Vjasal: HYPE PogChamp
reesync: PogChamp
session_variable: HYPEE
loopylol: LOL
Sunce_: scam train LUL
annestion41: SCAM TRAIN PogChamp
bubblesnot: @georgehotz do you have a paid Snapchat account?
krystalgamer: bottom 5 to top 5
name100015: PogChamp
thetimetraveler253: @georgehotz have you tried the steroids Jeff Bezos is on
robinduckett: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer100
blasio115: LOL
gtnftw: make some grilled cheese for us
SanJacobs: SCAM TRAIN
session_variable: onlyfans link?
zennydmt: whats ur favorite NY restaurant
leiterLAB: NINJA codes now ?
Vjasal: woah a countdown PogChamp
RAMBOxBEAST: Hi
loopylol: drop a water bottle "accidentally"
world2vec: suuuup gang
annestion41: AMAZING PogChamp
ApolloGo: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1
robinduckett: hahaha
annestion41: WAOW PogChamp
ay420notbannedlmao: test test test
abs412000: Hey Georrgy
eldac_kno: make donate option
rdrgcnt: you are a good cam girl geo
Sunce_: FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan
Faceless_Bard: backdoor action
solitaryyy: whipcream stream
blasio115: LOL
5GToren: hello good sir
Sleeper009: cheer2
00warl0k00: waszzzzsssup
ay420notbannedlmao: master bait?
alexmchugh: if u had donation based messages u would make a ton
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans?
NatePh_07: LOL
elpol1234: 4K for rent? WTF? Where do you live?
CJslider14: this is like /r/programmerhummor meets camboi
goobygoobler: get a wig man
Incurs0: Good morning George and chat :) /
eldac_kno: make donations to ask you questions
stanstill: get the whipped cream out
TomatoePasta: FeelsBadMan no masturbating on stream
bubblesnot: LOL
Sunce_: LULLULLUL
axlebear: Kappa
prittiao22: yo geo, how did u downloaded the wikipedia ??
rdrgcnt: lol
joiput: LUL
ericvaneri9k: ericvaneri9k subscribed at Tier 1.
Plurmorant: monkaS
Geniusz_Hamcia: xd
braineraser: lmao
zennydmt: did you move from CA to NY?
AerisThor: LUL
Hypheus_: LUL
Aqualyn: :(
cefaloclever: KEKW
gtnftw: we wanna see your sexy coding skills LUL
marschr: full pewdiepew cooking hot dogs
Faceless_Bard: she has data too LUL
sw1jari: Sadge
Sunce_: None those are special type of men monkaS
robinduckett: I came here for the code
stanstill: SAVAGE
Vjasal: if i give you money will something vibrate?
annestion41: FeelsBadMan
leiterLAB: FeelsBadMan
TekniqueTrading: I FEEL ATTACKED
5GToren: is it describing me
BigBurrito_09: FeelsBadMan
blasio115: FeelsBadMan
solitaryyy: lmao the demographics
SnakeOneMLG: :(
21_savior: FeelsBadMan
Hypheus_: OMEGALUL wtf
Sunce_: FeelsBadMan Same
patrickgekko: hahahaha
axlebear: me :)
Sleeper009: True
goobygoobler: SwiftRage SwiftRage SwiftRage
1donald: FeelsBadMan
ay420notbannedlmao: aahahah thats literally me
phrixus_bro: AWKWARD
fishpizza: FeelsBadMan
blasio115: alkXD
Dautlog: FeelsBadMan
session_variable: lol
ImNotTrolling: Sadge
axlebear: Too far
rdrgcnt: :(
leiterLAB: monkaS psychology
DadsWithoutKids: i'm clearly being targeted
ImNotTrolling: pepeHands
Locksdn: BibleThump
ImNotTrolling: widepeepoSad
bienisms: bienisms subscribed at Tier 1.
lightofhel1: lightofhel1 subscribed at Tier 1.
rdrgcnt: lol
robinduckett: ScaredyCat
NatePh_07: I feel attacked
Sunce_: 🦍 My man
EhGuyInCanada: georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans??
thetimetraveler253: I want to sub to george in front of all you little men
andRoStyle: Hi :)
NatePh_07: NotLikeThis
B1_Renekton: widePeepoSad
Digital_donger: these strategies PogChamp
zakara_: woah this is secret information
loopylol: wooooOooOOo
Aqualyn: LUL
TusKaN_BaNaNas: is this what you did instead of making a busy beaver test lol
rdrgcnt: looooooooool
burgerlove_: EXCLUDE US NOW
tommy_clash: 4Head
Faceless_Bard: so many of those things apply for twitch too LUL
eldac_kno: dude you need to make donate button to ask you questions
joaovictorsnt: hello
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans?
Vinndy: bro just make people feel like you're their friend and profit, that's how twitch works
blasio115: alkDMCA
krystalgamer: george the new e-girl
stanstill: woooOoOOOOOOo
Silver5005: I knew women were evil...........
ay420notbannedlmao: KEKW
goobygoobler: jesus who wrote this
Incurs0: I joined at a weird time LUL
robinduckett: lol onlyfans is just binary models
Sunce_: Shamless LUL
UnnamedEntity: Aella doesn't pull punches.
B1_Renekton: any gifters?
annestion41: Jebaited
gigafact: go go
THENEXTMOSES: when you subscribe but dont get a shout out :(
AerisThor: so never LUL
antiratt: @georgehotz why the word Кеуbоard is blocked? LOL
andRoStyle: andRoStyle subscribed at Tier 1.
eax_ebx: The content we deserve.
B1_Renekton: hypetrain never stops
biniar_: first 500, now hype train LOL
thetimetraveler253: i gotta go pee. don't release the test yet
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans??
ay420notbannedlmao: not happening KEKW
999void: i got an ad:/
bubblesnot: Lol no way he made a test
ericvaneri9k: do ittttt
the0n1: what is happening PogChamp
leiterLAB: NINJA is back on twitch PogChamp
999void: adblock is usless on twitch
Sunce_: @georgehotz u need to watch more trainwreckstv stream LUL to gain subs method
lightofhel1: SeemsGood
jamieemb_: This will start as a joke and end with George selling feet pics
Incurs0: omg LUL
Plurmorant: LUL
Aqualyn: LUL
Digital_donger: LUL
marschr: LOOOL
joaovictorsnt: I'll subscribe now to see the stream
antiratt: @georgehotz why the word Кеуbоard is blocked? LOL
qlutoo: What’s the test
metsu_gadoken: EleGiggle
cybergenik: sub to me :)
zennydmt: whats the best way to transport a monitor when moving
gigafact: wow George going full bananas
eax_ebx: Do we deserve it?
robinduckett: Camgirl programmer streamer
ay420notbannedlmao: gift to some girl in just chatting
Sunce_: HotPokket so ?
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans?
robinduckett: I'm sure there's some of those
porkaholic: true
sw1jari: @antiratt so ppl don't ask which one he uses i think
helofren: hi friends
Faceless_Bard: PepeHands
Digital_donger: FeelsBadMan
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans??
Silver5005: this is sick
annestion41: FeelsBadMan
Vjasal: true ;-;
bobsmash: sadge
leiterLAB: FeelsBadMan
Tishanskiii: I'm depressed now
Kubissus: PepeHands
MatiGoG: Sadge
ay420notbannedlmao: see if pokimane is streaming and become a real simp
gtnftw: helo fren
eldac_kno: handsome men do
TekniqueTrading: LUL
anguscupcake: tru
cefaloclever: True FeelsBadMan
SnakeOneMLG: stop reading pls, hurts too much
echotaco: Lol your stream can easily be carried by the quality of your content george, the vast majority of people will show up simply to be impressed by someone at the top of their field i.e. Hikaru in the chess category @georgehotz
B1_Renekton: WE ARE DOING SCIENCE BOIZ
TowlieGotHigh: FeelsBadMan True
lightofhel1: why do u need girl if u have twich chat KappaPride
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans?
abs412000: Hey why is it buffering so much
Digital_donger: any whales? PogChamp
sw1jari: @antiratt yeah it's in the stream description
bubblesnot: Simp to subs
Sole164: oh my is this the legendary blackra1n hotz PogChamp thanks for jb 10 yrs ago LUL
TekniqueTrading: not actually true bois
Plurmorant: im a whale for george
playful_fellow: wauv.. this is pretty pathetic.. ;D
Sunce_: esfandM yess whales esfandM esfandM esfandM
annestion41: ANY OIL PRINCES? PogChamp
goobygoobler: any oilers?
metsu_gadoken: Whales DansGame
leiterLAB: LuL
robinduckett: I'm in Wales, not the same thing tho
slava_llll: have you adressed the comments on the pool about the search engine you made on youtube?
homebr3w: So, are you technically whale fishing? Kappa
i_Memberino: btc traders in chat
porkaholic: i did that :)
Digital_donger: OIL PRINCES GET IN HERE PogChamp
norflin221: Kappa
Faceless_Bard: anyone rich people in chat ? type 1
EhGuyInCanada: georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans??
Sunce_: Any whales in chat PogChamp ?
ay420notbannedlmao: yeah but drugs instead od startups
Vjasal: im not rich... YET
prittiao22: yo im poor af
gtnftw: catfishing, but it's whalefishing now
B1_Renekton: ofc we did that
Cryptic___: Any oil princes, any tiger owners?
rhytual: LUL
antiratt: @sw1jari W I E R D
zakara_: like why can't it just be giants, I don't wanna be called a whale
Aqualyn: <- 🐋
Locksdn: YEP
leiterLAB: 4Head just sell a startup chat
21_savior: Kappa
marschr: sell bathing water
helofren: george going to CB?
bubblesnot: This article seems sexist...
i_Memberino: @georgehotz you need to stop talking about going on dates now LUL
B1_Renekton: B R A N D I N G
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans?
robinduckett: "dealing with the emotional burden" jfc
annestion41: 5Head
ay420notbannedlmao: brooo u promised test @ 500
mlejva: You also should start OnlyFans at some point! @georgehotz
Sunce_: LUL LUL LUL LUL
damooooooooooh: Wales isn't only the fish with the biggest dick in the ocean, it's also a country in the UK
B1_Renekton: LULW
Aqualyn: NotLikeThis
goobygoobler: who wrote this
eldac_kno: make donation button to ask question
eax_ebx: Do we deserve it?
Atrix321: when did the stream start?
bhad: trick people into money
5GToren: what are you reading bro xD
Sunce_: PogChamp
Faceless_Bard: good article , link
Aqualyn: WutFace
session_variable: wait whatt
BossCalifornia: We are ready
Aqualyn: uhh...
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what’s your OnlyFans?
anguscupcake: Hi poki :heart: i just wanted to say i really love you and i want to go on a date with you i’m the one who drops 20$ on your stream everyday you can dm if you want :relaxed: i have the last 130$ on my paypal that i’m gonna drop next stream just so we can meet ilysm i want to date really bad
NatePh_07: failed at first question
leiterLAB: TriHard always free
georgehotz: https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdSzC0GTMV2zwa9jZnUGGAv-ItZI8r78DOXqDNjhnzhq01JCw/viewform?usp=sf_link
bubblesnot: @georgehotz do the total opposite of this article...lol
eax_ebx: Is it Skinner box?
helofren: LOL question 1 : "are you a sub?" answer:yes, test = passed
session_variable: oh god
joaovictorsnt: the link ?????
pxlluu: https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdSzC0GTMV2zwa9jZnUGGAv-ItZI8r78DOXqDNjhnzhq01JCw/viewform?usp=sf_link
cefaloclever: 5Head test
infinex2: monkaS didnt read the paper
norflin221: what is Raven's 1?
session_variable: i just started watching like two days ago i don't know this
Atrix321: i didnt
NatePh_07: so the paper gets transform into IQ test LUL
ishammahajan: Scam train nice
world2vec: i'm too dumb for this
bhad: the first one is your own username
Faceless_Bard: whisper me the answers
JAKWAI: can u give me the link?
sw1jari: i'm just here for the intro :) didn't have time to watch the other streams FeelsBadMan
cutza: it's hard
georgehotz: https://forms.gle/EEuzAdDQB3hPZoUL7
Sunce_: wtf is this test monkaS oh shit
foti_kasparov: post the link
Den_dp: question about sub: right answer is yes Kappa
foti_kasparov: again
jsnfly: what can we win?
helofren: this is stupid, i read this shit and this test looks like its in spanish
Aqualyn: It's very hard sir I'm sweating 😫
homebr3w: Open book? Kappa
neilsweb: I made a typo in my name :-(
antiratt: wait.. what?
foti_kasparov: Link ?
krystalgamer: ewww turing
helofren: YES I READ IT
PigeonsDontFlyFar: Can find my cock? @georgehotz Pretty please. It's somewhere in the den.
BossCalifornia: Im putting 69 for the ones I dont know
porkaholic: what paper :)
myaocat: this is hard monkaW
Hypheus_: we were supposed to read a paper?
Hypheus_: monkaS
cucker: link?
BernardoFire: BernardoFire subscribed at Tier 1.
infinex2: monkaS
업넙업넙: which paper monkaS
itzahmerob: LOL
BossCalifornia: I didnt read the paper george im sorry
antiratt: which paper
pat95_: This the guy that hacked sony?
BossCalifornia: Please be nice to me
leiterLAB: paper ?
neilsweb: I made a typo in my username :-(
session_variable: If it takes 10 dogs 10 years to make 10 castles, how many years does it take 100 dogs to make 100 castles?
BernardoFire: s2
session_variable: LOL
stanstill: i cant write 10 to power of 34000
lightofhel1: need to learn how to read to pass the test NotLikeThis
Digital_donger: oh yes the paper pootheOk
Locksdn: FeelsBadMan i havent started calculus yet
antiratt: toilet paper?
FargioFarmani: Is it raining inside Georges flat?
gtnftw: lmao my test is a troll
helofren: I value the idea of goehot.
Incurs0: LUL
annestion41: LUL
helofren: dafuq is this voice hahahahaha
cutza: I gave up on the test
axlebear: PepoG
infinex2: jermaJup1 jermaJup2
infinex2: jermaJup3 jermaJup4
antiratt: KEKW
Kubissus: LUL
Locksdn: truth in a post-truth world
marschr: american gloria borger
BossCalifornia: Whats the answer for question 6 dont tell the teacher
KryekGG: Sexy wet look. Also you are balding
infinex2: last message in chat because ill fail the test monkaS
foti_kasparov: Can I do the test in Fall semester please? @georgehotz
krystalgamer: 69420
1stprinciples: What paper is he referring to?
bubblesnot: Did I pass coach @georgehotz ?
antiratt: @BossCalifornia 4
zakara_: reading hate comments live PogChamp
itzahmerob: Charmin is the best
KryekGG: Sexy wet look George. Also seems like you are balding, get that rogaine game on ! :D
buzzd24: imagine worshipping google unironically
ay420notbannedlmao: buy chainlink
bubblesnot: N word
myaocat: what to write if i dont know?
Plurmorant: OPEN SOURCE
Translogical: read the whole comment
Silver5005: ETH is changing the world
Silver5005: but okay
5GToren: what is that with your jaw
krystalgamer: what's the paper @georgehotz
infinex2: monkaS
itzahmerob: go to newest
sw1jari: google bad 😡
prittiao22: yo geo, how did u downloaded the wikipedia ??
Aqualyn: uh no :(
ay420notbannedlmao: NO CHAINS ONLY LINKS
ShredderSherlock: !test
cutza: gave up
Sunce_: monkaS 👍 good
ApolloGo: how old are you georgehotz badukb22 badukb22 badukb22
bienisms: I missed a good chunk of the lecture
bubblesnot: I thought you said the test would be multiple choice @georgehotz
Translogical: Read the whole comment, the one that you read first and try to respond seriously instead of reading it with a mocking voice
ay420notbannedlmao: antisemitism incoming
5GToren: Where is the paper we had to read at
JakeJ24: I'm just here to support the hockey stick growth
zakara_: SNEAKER BOOT
Hypheus_: pig things :)
itzahmerob: LOL
MEATCHOPS: pig things
thetimetraveler253: George would you ever go on an elk hunt
cutza: lol just reply "smash that thumbs up button"
mykes1777: literally just came here wtf he talkin xD
Incurs0: LUL
5GToren: LOL
damooooooooooh: Yo George, what about a Decentralized society? Would a decentralized subscription based society be more powerful than the US?
ShredderSherlock: ah, social darwinism at the core of thinking
BernardoFire: that was rough
myaocat: PogChamp Smart
Plurmorant: TRUE
livehoc: @georgehotz I have a referall code to the google foobar coding challenge, I know you like to do coding challenges on stream if you want the link lmk.
r00tkey: True.
sw1jari: REAL
ay420notbannedlmao: woah blm dude
rondon_squad: racism is the real virus TransgenderPride
5GToren: I quit, math 2 hard
prittiao22: yo geo, how did u downloaded the wikipedia ??
foti_kasparov: Can I pass the class without today's homework?
mykes1777: 5Head
arbitrandomuser: ah man Hacking .. i wish more people read RMS's post on hacking
aar0npham: send the test ink
myaocat: i only answered 3
robodemia: kluless george
infinex2: i cant read monkaS
spma0001: algun español
itzahmerob: I did the HW
buzzd24: i want the link
marschr: mass hiring strategy lol
tommy_clash: SoonerLater
georgehotz: https://forms.gle/eztnbvoJLHP65Czj7
Cryptic___: 665 monkaS
FargioFarmani: @georgehotz is it raining inside your flat?
infinex2: im reading the paper right now monkaS
ianisprinz: What do you think about kanye??
henistein: I wanto to hack NASA using html
Vjasal: 90% of viewers are bots monkaS
ozzy_1024: what happened to your hair?
rdrgcnt: What do you think about kanye??
dejvid1998: Is Papa George sweating so much because of amphetamines?
session_variable: Stallman is cool
world2vec: didnt even try to do the test, too dumb
Aqualyn: 1 MINUTE REMAINING SabaPing
anguscupcake: can u use calculators
eldac_kno: what do you think about piracy?
Sunce_: D:
Vegehi: BEEP BOOP
Incurs0: MrDestructoid
slava_llll: BloodTrail
JAKWAI: oh that will be embarissing ^^
robinduckett: I would participate but I havent been on the stream for a while and I'm not actually subscribed right now :P
업넙업넙: MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoid
Kriminell00: yes :)
strminftr: !form
xt3r: lelelel
Sunce_: MrDestructoid Hello world
dr_set: MrDestructoid
cefaloclever: MrDestructoid
JakeJ24: MrDestructoid
xt3r: cant open link rip
cutza: what's the bell distribution of your audience regarding skillset?
HopZe: MrDestructoid BEEP BOOP BEEP
Sunce_: PogChamp
Blacked0ut: Have you made any progress on proving or disproving we are in a simulation?
robinduckett: I think I got the Ravens questions though lol
krystalgamer: thanks dad
tommy_clash: MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoid MrDestructoid OptimizePrime OptimizePrime
axlebear: I gave up on the Turing part Sadge
Hypheus_: shit i didnt put my real username monkaS
itzahmerob: Ok ok George I didn't do the hw ):
ay420notbannedlmao: ez VIP
gtnftw: oh I didn't even think about the raven questions
Mal30: shit man, im to late to calss
TowlieGotHigh: NameError: name 'np' is not defined this is what python returns LUL
gtnftw: I just put 3 for everything
Mal30: just started the test
Hypheus_: you didnt send the paper BabyRage
Sunce_: esfandYou esfandAre esfandDead
krystalgamer: LMFAO
flaczq: there was a paper to read? monkaS
strminftr: link? :P
HEB30P0B: PogChamps thx for 5 minutes
Blacked0ut: @georgehotz Have you made any progress on proving or disproving we are in a simulation?
bienisms: What's the link to the paper?
slava_llll: link the paper for chirst sake)
Translogical: read the youtube comment as a whole
Aqualyn: MaxLOL
leiterLAB: FailFish ?
Mal30: YEAH... Im working hard here
itzahmerob: CYA Pigeon
robinduckett: I didn't know there'd be a test lol
infinex2: monkaS im still reading
NatePh_07: LUL
AerisThor: he did Hypheus_
alexmchugh: lol academic paper
neilsweb: I put my username as georgehotz. Is that hacking?
slava_llll: SOMEONE LINK THE PAPER
lithiumx4900: what is this test and where do I take it?
gtnftw: You can use Fossabot
AerisThor: it was spammed on chat lol
1stprinciples: what paper are you referring to?
NatePh_07: just submitted and pray for my luck
Hypheus_: missed it PepeHands @AerisThor
KanadaCheese: @georgehotz did you use arduino?
michaelkawwa: bruh
robinduckett: nope!
AerisThor: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
sw1jari: fair
AerisThor: this is the paper
itzahmerob: Need Paper PLS
iskjmss: imagine not watching yesterday's streams smh
michaelkawwa: hes too much
homebr3w: Good thing I am "Skipping class" today Kappa
JAKWAI: I just watched a numberphile video on busy beaver :/
porkaholic: just wont do the test then 😎
AerisThor: but i didnt read it not ognna lie lol
leiterLAB: no paper still answered TriHard
ay420notbannedlmao: thats cheating
Hypheus_: awful professor 0/10 :)
lightofhel1: school of life
JAKWAI: lets see ^^
Locksdn: D:
EhGuyInCanada: can you submit more than one response? @georgehotz
GReeN_HuMaN: I am late for the test
bubblesnot: @georgehotz why are we allowed to talk? We are not worthy senpai.
axlebear: I can’t watch hotz streams all day every day
goobygoobler: im shooting for 50%
sw1jari: that timeout idea is actually good
lesserthangood: @georgehotz whats ur opinion on the new taylor swift
kklisura: My dog just ate the test. :|
TowlieGotHigh: LUL
helofren: i watched that vid too, he said there are still machine running from way back then form 5 cards hahaha
itzahmerob: That boar comment was hilarious lmao
isaac123garris: The answer is 42
session_variable: if i do the test i will fail
myaocat: nightbot
gtnftw: Fossabot
Sunce_: nightbot
leiterLAB: MrDestructoid
itzahmerob: Yes pls
KanadaCheese: the only test i passed so far
EhGuyInCanada: bruh why is half of this an IQ test LMAO
goobygoobler: lol
krystalgamer: busy beaver more like A+
NatePh_07: there is a slow mode somewhere?
Plurmorant: no pls
Warbayx: monkaS
myaocat: https://nightbot.tv/
BrodatyWhiteBear: monkaS
B1_Renekton: monkaW
lithiumx4900: damn. woke up, tuned in, and I'm late for a test I never knew I had
Repunk: ew node
leiterLAB: MrDestructoid monkaS
Koduck007: DailyHotz
gtnftw: fossabot & nightbot are the most popular
Sunce_: no Mods no bots sachio1Comfy stream <3
MatiGoG: make it in rust Pog
bubblesnot: This should be a twitch stream about building a better twitch stream
5GToren: make it in coq
lesserthangood: POGGERS
Joooooooooonas: nightbot is pretty nice
neilsweb: I put my name as georgehotz. You going to ban yourself. HAKED
krystalgamer: geroge's boomer shows in these moments
LightBringer009: it should be easier with nightbot
BrodatyWhiteBear: MrDestructoid 🔪 monkaS
strminftr: "Extensive API"
gtnftw: check Fossabot and compare feature sets
gigafact: no it does not do what you want
myaocat: make a bot in ARM ASM Kappa
biniar_: Channel points to talk
Lintelligence: Lintelligence subscribed with Twitch Prime.
eax_ebx: IT'S TERROR!
dolchebeats: The test felt like a normal math test to me, didnt know a single answer
lesserthangood: 10 year follower mode only
1stprinciples: rofl
michaelkawwa: wheres the test yall
5GToren: Hahaha!
itzahmerob: LOL
porkaholic: stpeach Kreygasm
Hypheus_: oh no here we go LUL
Plurmorant: LUL
helofren: bro
thetimetraveler253: lol
rhytual: LUL peach
leiterLAB: monkaS 👉 MrDestructoid
B1_Renekton: lol
ay420notbannedlmao: simp
buzzd24: LUL
helofren: hes about to discover her ass.
antiratt: nice peach
b0n3rfeast: coooomer
komisarz_bagieta: LUL
itzahmerob: Eh?
thetimetraveler253: simp
rhytual: check out her instagram
bobbincat: LUL
NatePh_07: LUL
Joooooooooonas: You could put in Emote Only and then Mod them, so they can write
buzzd24: SIMP
EhGuyInCanada: SIMP
sw1jari: canada ay
Makouvios: OH NO
TomatoePasta: check ig LUL
asmonmaldin: LUL
slava_llll: lmao
i_Memberino: coomer LUL
kklisura: lol
lightofhel1: nordvpn POGU
hrittik166: Are u actually going to ban everyone who didn't do well
Lintelligence: "distracted"
NatePh_07: DM her pls
Sunce_: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
homebr3w: casual LUL
altic: lul
krystalgamer: SIMP
porkaholic: CHECK HER IG Kreygasm
helofren: he doged it, whew
myaocat: LUL
bobbincat: test finished now
kachokblexinity: Javascript The Best! Python for Noobs
gigafact: you will need to code your own bot
Repunk: I don't think twitch would like a username whitelist like that lol
bubblesnot: I failed but I’m a sub so teacher will bump my grade
axlebear: HOOMER
Koduck007: wow just a 20 hour drive lmao
sw1jari: i followed :)
rahLLi: no
arbitrandomuser: coursewedo
JAKWAI: sure
Den_dp: according to what we read earlier - she has a bf
cutza: stpeach confirmed George's waifu
MyLoveSachan: no :)
gtnftw: "Are you outside?" - George 2020
leiterLAB: sure Kappa
NatePh_07: ofc, who doesn't
KanadaCheese: Your instagram is so funny :D
triple__m: I'm not following on insta, thats not part of the test
MEATCHOPS: look at this guy, on a swing all by himself, such a big boy
TusKaN_BaNaNas: how many test responses?
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz can we stay in the chat if we follow you on instagram?
Vrookems: that 5th pic is cyber af
lesserthangood: whats ur onlyfans
thetimetraveler253: what's with that ig profile pic
homebr3w: post more, and I probably will
bubblesnot: You dont post
r00tkey: Bots are hotz.
I__Zer0__I: Ofc Kappa
TurkTurkelton: lol imagine using any facebook products in 2020
hrittik166: Yes I follow you on Insta. If I don't do well on the test don't ban me
asdhxc: can I have a link
robinduckett: how do you deal with constant distractions in general? I feel like I can't get anything done at the moment
WantRe: !test
Free3ze: KappaCool 🍹
Plurmorant: monkaS I'm still computing busy beaver numbers
foti_kasparov: SEARCH GOOGLE FOR IMAGE
DomFrags: 109 responses 109 bans
itzahmerob: Wait is insta a part of the test?
Warbayx: monkaS
michaelkawwa: if your dumb you cant talk
Lintelligence: where's the test
adroniser: where is test
world2vec: yes but you dont post anything there
isaac123garris: The only answer is 42
Sunce_: LUL
neilsweb: Just 20hr drive. You're less than one day away.
michaelkawwa: nice
ay420notbannedlmao: do we get a certificate is we pass?
iskjmss: mute fetish confirmed
arbitrandomuser: no one else can talk !?
BossCalifornia: I would like you to delete my test entry under GDPR
asdhxc: can someone link it
perrierking: !test
jsnfly: can we retake the test?
riskyclix: riskyclix subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Lintelligence: i just joined - where's the test? haha
leiterLAB: monkaS IQ opressive chat
arbitrandomuser: for eternity ?
adroniser: !test
ay420notbannedlmao: wanna put it in my curriculum
robinduckett: how do you deal lol
Free3ze: monkaS
5GToren: haha
hardtarget4: link bro
michaelkawwa: wheres the test????
Hypheus_: monkaS
itzahmerob: BUT BUT
Incurs0: :(
breadhamandegg: link?
hrittik166: Yes I follow you on Insta. If I don't do well on the test don't ban me
melkeydev: Yo @georgehotz answer - What are your thoughts on GP3
Aqualyn: LUL
infinex2: monkaS
helofren: create a chat channel with a pw and only allow the people who passed to enter?
Warbayx: but im dumb monkaS
biniar_: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
robinduckett: I love getting a zero
breadhamandegg: sadge
biniar_: damn wrong link
arbitrandomuser: For how long is this ban ?
itzahmerob: Gimme more time to read paper pls
asmonmaldin: MonkaS
asdhxc: rip
Hypheus_: i put my name as IDontWantToGetBanned monkaS
fishpizza: monkaS I'm a new viewer
TusKaN_BaNaNas: Yeah if i dont show up to the midterm that means I dont have to take it right?
iskjmss: LUL
breadhamandegg: i enjoyed my stay chat <3
arbitrandomuser: Whats the syllabus for tomorrows test?
leiterLAB: LUL
bakuldada: what if onlyy 10 people did well in the test
Plurmorant: fake quiz ez
iskjmss: can't you still make it a quiz?
krystalgamer: LMFAO
B1_Renekton: dont worry guys we run an alt chat for the stream
michaelkawwa: its literally an iq test lmao
Fulk33: @georgehotz about the discussion on a "bitcoin society" from 2 streams ago: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meritocracy
homebr3w: @georgehotz I've decided to use my free homework pass for this assignment. I hope you understand Kappa
antiratt: reroll
jawbre9ker: youre failing the google docs test
KanadaCheese: you have to hack tesla's autopilot to begin the test
bobbincat: can't close a form Kappa
strminftr: invalidate the link maybe
michaelkawwa: so intelligence discrimination?
JakeJ24: on the responses tab
breadhamandegg: @B1_Renekton aka discord? Kappa
leiterLAB: can't close form LUL
MyLoveSachan: @georgehotz I'm knew to the stream. What do you do usually?
B1_Renekton: @georgehotz there is a twitch extension for quiz
lesserthangood: i never evn got the form PepeHands
Hypheus_: Pog got it right
MyLoveSachan: new*
ay420notbannedlmao: clap
Plurmorant: 300 iq PogChamp
asmonmaldin: PepeHands I want to chat
CollinPCO: yes
Mal30: no 3Head
JAKWAI: yea they go apart a bit more every time
NatePh_07: horizontal spacing
Locksdn: 2 easy
B1_Renekton: 5Head
leiterLAB: WE GOT IT PogChamp
ay420notbannedlmao: no need to explain
krystalgamer: 100%
EhGuyInCanada: EASY IQ
Digital_donger: reee I didn't submit in time FeelsBadMan
axlebear: Racially biased test FeelsWeirdMan
krystalgamer: A++++++, thanks dad
CollinPCO: one together apart together and turned double apart
leiterLAB: googling answer pepelaf
breadhamandegg: elimination
MyLoveSachan: What does this guy do on stream?
asdhxc: Nice knowing you guys
dolchebeats: woo i got it right
projectfaro: put chat above your microwave
Free3ze: bye guys HeyGuys
cybergenik: I didn't know the turing machine questions ;(
mkdrmnd: so fat so good boys
CollinPCO: it is also process of elimination at a certain point
helofren: anyone else read this paper and feel dumb after the test?
CollinPCO: a lot of things dont make sense
TomatoePasta: last spam Sadge
death_gadget: @axlebear You forgot the Kappa
robinduckett: new test for next time? this might be a niche
ay420notbannedlmao: no need to explain ...
gtnftw: A -> E -> 7
miche_____: 7
spma0001: did people execute Q3 in python?
MyLoveSachan: @georgehotz what do you do on stream?
breadhamandegg: 2?
Hypheus_: LUL
itzahmerob: LOL
sw1jari: Pepega Clap
miche_____: seven
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz can you give us a makeup test?
many_mangos: iq tests are so easy to pass
miche_____: 7
martinoestuessy: can we get a coding test please
foti_kasparov: 25
ay420notbannedlmao: ???
Hypheus_: EZ Clap
willarkitekt: ah missed the deadline
thetimetraveler253: blocked
homebr3w: Winner winner chicken dinner
buzzd24: LINEY
itzahmerob: so many LINEYS
thetimetraveler253: scroll up george
myaocat: can't see the answers
SnakeOneMLG: we cant see
myaocat: have you think about green screen?
ay420notbannedlmao: 10iq stream
helofren: oh, the geetarees
Free3ze: I cant C tyler1C
NatePh_07: put it on right screen pls
Hypheus_: LUL
spielprogrammierer: I could at least solve the Python code, 120389
itzahmerob: Lmaoooooo
axlebear: 5Head
Kubissus: LUL
Dautlog: LOL
Sunce_: D:
Lintelligence: lmfao
gtnftw: I put 3 for everything
CollinPCO: got none of the turning/computer stuff right but cause i know nothing and havent looked at anything
jawbre9ker: 69 wasnt right I ugess
codingquark: Hello! What are we doing today?
gtnftw: wait I put 2 for this one
TowlieGotHigh: i dont have np BabyRage
5GToren: docker?
DaChiimp: DaChiimp gifted a Tier 1 sub to martinoestuessy! This is their first Gift Sub in the channel!
tenken_sj: LUL
robinduckett: the dev/null doesn't return 0 for exit code 0?
homebr3w: got em
helofren: @gtnftw me too
sw1jari: someone said i don't have np PepeLaugh
Repunk: had to use wsl for that one lol
ay420notbannedlmao: daSimp
myaocat: so how is it 39?
bobbincat: we all on windows LUL
buzzd24: LUL
Warbayx: LUL
breadhamandegg: LUL
spielprogrammierer: strange, the Python returned 120389 on my system, Python3 on Debian
TheRealMast3r: i'm on phone
Plurmorant: D:
Hypheus_: too much effort
Incurs0: LUL
julen9601: what is he doing?
HEB30P0B: LUL
Repunk: LMAO
NatePh_07: LUL
numbblol: LUL
aar0npham: kinda funny
flaczq: i did this one on paper
norflin221: dude i have windows
OG_KNOCC_OUT: LUL
fishpizza: IM ON IPHONE LULW
r00tkey: LOL
infinex2: monkaS
TowlieGotHigh: i didn't know about np BabyRage i don't program math
helofren: we tried doing it in our HEDS
bubblesnot: I’m on iPad
Mayfieldiv: trolled me with windows..
myaocat: i copied it to python on OSX and it print 120389 :D
Warbayx: im on nokia
itzahmerob: LOL
luspr: what is going on here ? coding test for the viewers?
dr_set: shit, the test is way easier than I imagined, I should have tried even if I didn't do the homework
michaelkawwa: didnt take calculus yet
MyLoveSachan: NA EDUCATION
thetimetraveler253: teach calculus
helofren: i put 6x :(
world2vec: my python in ubuntu gave wrong answer,feck
iskjmss: imagine getting the derivative wrong LUL
MyLoveSachan: NA EDUCATION LULW
Vegehi: thats cheating Kappa
HEB30P0B: 4Head just go wolframalpha
Coshbuc: isn't that cheating?
session_variable: you didn't say we could cheat??
itzahmerob: ME DONT LIKE MATH
sw1jari: @Coshbuc well at least be 'smart' enough to cheat
newlastaccount: this chat will only contain 3 people
Plurmorant: im too ethical NotLikeThis
spielprogrammierer: I did wolfram alpha for the next question :-) "y - 5 = x + 3, solve x", got x=y-8, used y=0
thetimetraveler253: not ethical
porkaholic: no :)
Sunce_: Wolfram PogChamp he is an og
leander_ms: That is not cool 🤬
Free3ze: nope ;)
eax_ebx: LOL
Vinndy: i literally googled all the questions and got them
biniar_: the test was rigged
TomatoePasta: cheating DansGame
julen9601: LMAO
ay420notbannedlmao: но
thetimetraveler253: don't use google after last stream
many_mangos: LUL
Lintelligence: BE RESOURCEFUL
r00tkey: nahamsHackerman
slimpimp007: shambles LUL
Sunce_: Cheating DansGame
Lintelligence: it's called life
j0ebee_: How come I missed this test?
homebr3w: @georgehotz They didn't get the python one done. You think they are gonna paste a derivative in LUL
NatePh_07: we follow honor code
itzahmerob: BEST TEACHER EVER
codingquark: what, there was some test?!
lithiumx4900: It's basic calculus. Like first day of class calculus.
Lintelligence: resourcefulness = the true skill you need in life
antiratt: hackers ktkEZ
ay420notbannedlmao: 65 кекш
Mal30: LETS SHAME THE ONES, WHO ANSWERED 100
gtnftw: ayyyy 69
leiterLAB: NotLikeThis
bubblesnot: I said 100
leander_ms: GEORGE TEACH ME DADDY
butyesss: so the chat wll be 4 people
axlebear: Depends on the dogs roles 5Head
Mayfieldiv: gutless goanna
buzzd24: we cant see
B1_Renekton: it said 25
B1_Renekton: people
Free3ze: 5GToren
butyesss: ah lol
j0ebee_: When was this test taken?
5GToren: yo?
Free3ze: @j0ebee_ 5 mins ago
TowlieGotHigh: oh so its the middle number that writes the 1 KEKW
porkaholic: @epicdubstepremix
JakeJ24: This is a wisdom of the crowds in action. If we take the median we all get 100%
Sunce_: 1337 LUL wtf
leander_ms: We are all just dumb and want to watch the master here
leiterLAB: LUL
Free3ze: LUL
thetimetraveler253: why doesn't the halting state count
j0ebee_: @Free3ze thanks
helofren: this. test. is. a. bag. of. SHIT
Sunce_: someone typed 420 CiGrip answers
helofren: :)
JAKWAI: I should learn for my real exams and Im concerned about my busy beaver test >.<
31337cr3w: hey guys, i just got here. Where can i take the test before i hear the answers?
leiterLAB: FeelsBadMan
spielprogrammierer: no one read the paper :-)
Hypheus_: EZ Clap
dolchebeats: idk what a busy beaver is
iskjmss: ONLY 64 PEOPLE LUL
homebr3w: @thetimetraveler253 halt state doesn't write to tape
antiratt: 1337, 420
sw1jari: seems like no one even watched the stream
tenken_sj: i might have to re do this class again next year Kappa
antiratt: ez
neilsweb: banned
Hypheus_: i passed :)
sw1jari: oh
leander_ms: @dolchebeats nobody knows that is the meme
eax_ebx: Ору
sw1jari: TOS
leiterLAB: any 1337 ?
asdhxc: who passes?
itzahmerob: George make another test PLS
Plurmorant: monkaS
fishpizza: TOS
ay420notbannedlmao: ezpz
MEATCHOPS: Bye bros :(
spielprogrammierer: @dolchebeats see here: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
NatePh_07: what is the cutoff then LUL
5GToren: hahaha
MEATCHOPS: nice talking to you all
Hypheus_: LUL
Incurs0: D:
Mal30: hahahaa
sw1jari: kinda weird chat
leander_ms: cockboi LUL
Locksdn: D:
OG_KNOCC_OUT: sodUNSURE
neilsweb: How did you do on the test hotz?
ZURiE: cockboi is good to go
thetimetraveler253: just use the grading feature
Digital_donger: everyone passed PogChamp
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz can we have a makeup test please?
itzahmerob: Make a chart
itzahmerob: Fool
leander_ms: the names on here LUL
axlebear: BOOMER
strminftr: = 1 if answer == correct else 0
sw1jari: WutFace
leander_ms: You guys are not disappointing me LUL
tenken_sj: WutFace
butyesss: yes
kolmok0dz: easier to make a table first
Sunce_: WutFace
Mlewii: nooo I was late for the test --"
infinex2: wutface
foti_kasparov: We coding in Excel now
world2vec: geohot struggles with spreadsheets, I struggle with computer science, we're not the same
homebr3w: @georgehotz Will there be a curve Kappa
spielprogrammierer: most likely the higher grades have less inappropriate user names
Lintelligence: lmfaoooo
DadsWithoutKids: good thing it wasn't an excel test
Vjasal: LUL
Fulk33: EQ
neilsweb: we build a can classifier to catch inappropriate user names based on test results.
Free3ze: LUL
Lintelligence: hacks iphone but doesn't know Excel formulas
FMxnz_: squadR
raad1masum: this is geohot learning a new lang
NatePh_07: its not C++ LUL
robinduckett: oh god
Manch___: LUL
TowlieGotHigh: LUL
FargioFarmani: This is going to be a long stream
bravech: you have to use IF
TomatoePasta: excel programming PogChamp
ay420notbannedlmao: IF
krystalgamer: dmh
B1_Renekton: i have no idea how sheets works
1whoknew: @Lintelligence hahah
sw1jari: aight bye chat good luck with busy beaver
krystalgamer: george
ZURiE: mods PS4... can't use excel
prakyath_kantharaju: use pandas its so easy
itzahmerob: IF
thetimetraveler253: ResidentSleeper
gzero1889: OK EXCELL TUTORIAL PogChamp
krystalgamer: struggling hard
DeeboMC: @mlewii yea I missed a key stream as well apparently
livehoc: @georgehotz You can use JS on Google Sheets
UnnamedEntity: did... did you not set the form up to autograde
helofren: being a sub = 5 points @georgehotz
tenken_sj: LUL
5GToren: now u can drag it down I think
JohnnyThe_Hobo: 69 nice
foti_kasparov: LUL
Locksdn: LUL
zamorai123: use it as csv - dataframe
prakyath_kantharaju: use pandas
fishpizza: LUL 69 guy
sw1jari: one of my profs writes papers on excel lol
metsu_gadoken: LUL
hrittik166: I am dying from inside. I forgot to type 1 in the derivative out of excitement
itzahmerob: Nice
Lintelligence: excel programming = esoteric programming
leander_ms: That is the internet, it consists of 69 and 420
Sunce_: who typed 80085 LUL i did too
B1_Renekton: @georgehotz look at mine name : b1_renekton
world2vec: nice
sw1jari: body once told me
kolmok0dz: Date -> Create Filter
Lintelligence: can't sum T/F
antiratt: LOL
Lintelligence: lmao
Vjasal: true + true = 0
myaocat: =SUM(::)
NatePh_07: count true man
fishpizza: sum if true?
EhGuyInCanada: convert the booleans to 1 or 0
Lintelligence: if(True, 1, 0)
krystalgamer: COUNT TRUE
leander_ms: Do an if and then 1 for true
alexmchugh: count
drkolenklow: need to count
Lintelligence: switch to binary bro
Mal30: sum smash...?
DadsWithoutKids: today i learned that i know how to code better than georgehotz
father_goats: gavrilKamute gavrilKafacepalm
subtracting1: COUNTIF
alexmchugh: count count count
kolmok0dz: Data -> Create Filter to sort and filter
prakyath_kantharaju: use pandas its so easy
helofren: WoW aRe YoU NoT eVeN a HaCkEr!/!?!
marschr: the test should've contained excel questions lol
Lintelligence: pd.read_csv()
ZURiE: SUM....body once told me the world is gonna roll me I ain't the sharpest tool in the shed She was looking kind of dumb with her finger and her thumb In the shape of an "L" on her forehead…
bubblesnot: Hey teach what can i do for bonus points? I am going to need them to pass
spielprogrammierer: I would quickly code it in J or Python :-)
cutza: Google sheets Turing machine
5GToren: yeah turning grading on was better
deva73: what are these
dolchebeats: any way i can retake the test?
echotaco: Time to hire a TA haha
kklisura: Wow. Did not know you're an excel programmer. Nice.
siriusb_79: just download as json file
neilsweb: People idolize this guy as a programmer? He can't even use excel.
JohnnyThe_Hobo: wouldve been easier to hack google doc database servers by now than to finish this excel
ay420notbannedlmao: so slos
ay420notbannedlmao: slos
subtracting1: Why not write a vba macro?
ay420notbannedlmao: slow
ZURiE: this is like using console.log to bebug javascript
dolchebeats: could've just graded it within google forms
thetimetraveler253: i want to be a TA
breadhamandegg: me :)
krystalgamer: i do
krystalgamer: I'll be a TA
TowlieGotHigh: monkaS
Kodaly: im a good man
Sunce_: D:
Trindor_: ban me first
tenken_sj: monkaS
kolmok0dz: @neilsweb as opposed to be a Google sheets 733t would garner respect? hmm
Makouvios: MonkaS
gtnftw: I would be a TA but I failed the test LUL
Hypheus_: silenced :)
HEB30P0B: D:
OG_KNOCC_OUT: forsenS
Mal30: add a new question: whoever can make the excel work for you
fishpizza: monkaS WHAT
leander_ms: BAN ME DADDY
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what score do you need in order to be able to speak?
Kyoto_o: ban me first to prove the point @georgehotz
helofren: never subbing again, i just get called dumb everyday
thetimetraveler253: anyone else getting nervous
Fulk33: @georgehotz I just joined, will there be another quiz?
TowlieGotHigh: if u ban me, ill just make a new account :)
bubblesnot: I paid to speak in here
jotembruv: i just joined whats happening
Lintelligence: i have a doctor's note to why i was late and why i didn't take the test.
axlebear: monkaW
myaocat: https://www.python-excel.org/
Sunce_: i'm gettting nervous monkaS
CollinPCO: what about a curve teach
slava_llll: CAN WE HAVE IMMUNITY IF WE PAY :S
robinduckett: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 I take my eventual muting excitedly
gtnftw: he's grading our quiz
hrittik166: George is gonna ban us all
arbitrandomuser: will there be another test soon ?
DeeboMC: Cult’s coming along nicely, eh?
spielprogrammierer: @neilsweb good iPhone hackers are not necessarily good programmers as well
Kobayawaka: dont you need to change columns for answers
norflin221: @georgehotz so new ppl to the stream will never be able to chat?
deva73: waht quiz is this?
antiratt: quick selfie
1stprinciples: I do!
Lintelligence: mom?
ZURiE: GURLLLLLL
joaovictorsnt: lol
itzahmerob: Test boi
joaovictorsnt: girrrlll
TheRealMast3r: Ask her to pass the test
Sunce_: twitchy ?? DansGame
Vjasal: hi mom
NatePh_07: send her the test pls
ay420notbannedlmao: testing for covid
leander_ms: hi mom
axlebear: Milky mommy
Hypheus_: EZ
Incurs0: LUL
5GToren: lmfao
homebr3w: LUL
Digital_donger: Kappa
OG_KNOCC_OUT: Kappa
BrodatyWhiteBear: LUL
internetfro9: how are you guys unable to answer such easy questions
TomatoePasta: EZ
SnakeOneMLG: he is in
helofren: george got caught lurking?!?!?!
iskjmss: LUL
tenken_sj: exposed LUL
TowlieGotHigh: LUL
thetimetraveler253: fake laugh
slava_llll: lmao
SummerChroma: EZ
bubblesnot: I tested HIV positive
Vjasal: hi georgehotz's mom
Warbayx: LUL
metsu_gadoken: LUL
ay420notbannedlmao: ahaahah
Sunce_: twitchies LUL
Stoltmeister: LUL
hrittik166: Twitchies
eax_ebx: hi georgehotz's mom
antiratt: WAIT THAT WAS MY MOM!
robinduckett: twitchies roflmao
name100015: haHAA
helofren: george got caught liking a pic from 7 years ago
asdhxc: pay 2 win
Sunce_: esfandM esfandM esfandM
leander_ms: I did not participate in the test so I am looking fine
gtnftw: we should be able to buy in
goobygoobler: answer it
eax_ebx: It's @antiratt MOM!
slava_llll: PJSugar PJSugar PJSugar PJSugar
TowlieGotHigh: P2W YEP
Kubissus: damn it cliff
5GToren: doxed?
protectionfromblue: money on her mind, calls you out of the blue
Muzyd: p2w
gtnftw: how else will he "keep score"
krystalgamer: get a real phone
Trindor_: YEP P2W
neilsweb: If I pass, can I put it on my linkedin?
Locksdn: HeyGuys so long people
krystalgamer: not a iphone
Warbayx: hang up 🦍
foti_kasparov: Bye bye Alex
zennydmt: @ZURiE you play quake?
Sunce_: 🦍 My man
ay420notbannedlmao: DUMPED
helofren: girl gets on phone, george += sexy_pose()
world2vec: bye guys, was good while it lasted
gigafact: was that Alex?
itzahmerob: RIP to the facetime
neilsweb: Was that your mom?
cybergenik: I got everything up to the turing questions :(
internetfro9: 1337 guy LUL
prakyath_kantharaju: see you boys
bubblesnot: @georgehotz are you using zoom for phone calls now?
CollinPCO: i tried to buy myself into ND but my brother was in the process of dropping out while there so ...
iskjmss: we're twitchies guys :)
Sunce_: esfandW
slava_llll: how much will IMMUNITY COST?
internetfro9: 42069 guy LUL
julen9601: Is @georgehotz in love?
Kyoto_o: !test
NatePh_07: more than 10 questions LUL
antiratt: 69 420 ez
kolmok0dz: only 128 testers?
Lintelligence: who got 10?!?!
gigafact: graph that
Hypheus_: there was a 10 monkaS
TowlieGotHigh: YO THERES A 10 Pog
Trindor_: i saw a 10
julen9601: 0
Trindor_: wtf
iskjmss: BRUH
Cal3b123: Press F to pay respects for me
d4rkvist3r: can i still make the test?
tenken_sj: a 10 PogChamp
robinduckett: 100 bits for immunity
Kyoto_o: share the link chat
31337cr3w: i like the test idea for who can speak
Kyoto_o: share it
gtnftw: @Vjasal you got 7?!?!?!?
pvnieo: F
biniar_: scores of who submitted lol
itzahmerob: Sort filter
Trindor_: z to a
aar0npham: u have to make it as table first
arbitrandomuser: should have just used Pandas
gtnftw: If i did a bunch of 4's instead of a bunch of 3's I would've won
leander_ms: The first person is my hero, 69 for everything LUL
Incurs0: two 10's PogChamp
Hypheus_: LUL
Lintelligence: HAHAAAHA
breadhamandegg: PogChamp I WON
death_gadget: LUL
xolonexo: @georgehotz I think you're a great guy.
Sunce_: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
tenken_sj: F
Plurmorant: the elite
internetfro9: PogChamp
metsu_gadoken: LUL
hrittik166: what
helofren: you said 50%
Free3ze: Kappa
5GToren: no
miche_____: i scored 10 PogChamp
darkandfullofterrors: DuckerZ
numbblol: LUL
ay420notbannedlmao: KEKW
EhGuyInCanada: Make it a 3
slava_llll: how about 5
thetimetraveler253: you said 50
Hypheus_: 50 :)
Vjasal: @gtnftw ye moon2M
ZURiE: @georgehotz copy them and open their names so we can see who the heros are
itzahmerob: Make another test and I'll do the HW LOL
NatePh_07: 3
hrittik166: 3
solitaryyy: make it a 6
Hypheus_: 50% :)
robinduckett: I scored zero
internetfro9: 0
SnakeOneMLG: people who took the test pass
Plurmorant: D:
robinduckett: sorry bros
Sunce_: monkaS
Mal30: make the passing grade whatever a guy without the beaver shit is capable of
tommy_clash: Jebaited
fishpizza: there's 12 questions
siriusb_79: this iswhy we have no more innovation Sadge
Warbayx: D:
thetimetraveler253: feels bad man
Hypheus_: LUL
buzzd24: D:
Plurmorant: nooo
Incurs0: D:
OG_KNOCC_OUT: sodSAD
breadhamandegg: D:
myaocat: D:
nat0w: LUL
BrodatyWhiteBear: D:
world2vec: damnm, we're all ignorants
Sunce_: D:
internetfro9: LUL
world2vec: feels good
buzzd24: D: noo
TowlieGotHigh: D:
d4rkvist3r: lol
ay420notbannedlmao: bye
HEB30P0B: BibleThump
asdhxc: tfw you missed the test
Locksdn: D:
biniar_: That will show the chat who's boss
Trindor_: get rekt ignorants
1stprinciples: make it 5
Lintelligence: bronze 1 renekton
Mayfieldiv: trolled by windows..
Plurmorant: @B1_Renekton take my babies
AshirokSC: Pog
buzzd24: @B1_Renekton PogChamp
Vegehi: PogChamp
miche_____: B1_Renekton PogChamp
anon543264: @B1_Renekton
Hypheus_: @B1_Renekton PogChamp
FargioFarmani: @B1_Renekton
Warbayx: B1_Renekton PogU
SnakeOneMLG: bronze 1 renekton
leander_ms: @B1_Renekton that is a PogChamp
gtnftw: @B1_Renekton wow
BossCalifornia: @B1_Renekton
Lintelligence: bronze 1 renekton lmao
krystalgamer: ayy look at me
BrodatyWhiteBear: @B1_Renekton PogChamp
porkaholic: LEAGUE PLAYHERS LUL
ConagYuirg: ayyy I came 6th
jotembruv: @B1_Renekton Pog
Sunce_: @B1_Renekton PogChamp @B1_Renekton PogChamp @B1_Renekton PogChamp @B1_Renekton PogChamp @B1_Renekton PogChamp
Dautlog: @B1_Renekton PogChamp
5GToren: @B1_Renekton
B1_Renekton: Pog
tenken_sj: @B1_Renekton PogChamp
Kobayawaka: How 4098 is good answer for so many questions????
ZURiE: #RIGGED
hansgoebbels: what are we looking at
benjamindover146: god
Lintelligence: LoL poggers
antiratt: B1 4header
BossCalifornia: @B1_Renekton Pog
thetimetraveler253: @B1_Renekton
JohnnyThe_Hobo: actual genius
foti_kasparov: @B1_Renekton
Vjasal: @B1_Renekton PogChamp
AshirokSC: PogChamp
Incurs0: @B1_Renekton Clap
ay420notbannedlmao: @b1_renekton CLAP PogO
itzahmerob: All bow to me I am B1
slimpimp007: POG
hansgoebbels: I want to do this
Hypheus_: @AshirokSC PogChamp
tommy_clash: @B1_Renekton
pvnieo: PogChamp
cutza: SeemsGood
robinduckett: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer100
MatiGoG: forsenCD 2 timers
ConagYuirg: ay george I spelt my username wrong can I still be in
cybergenik: League player Pog
HopZe: @AshirokSC
Lintelligence: I have a legitimate reason as to why I was late to the stream and didn't take the test. Give me an all or nothing question
slimpimp007: Pog
buzzd24: LMFAO
Warbayx: VIP THEM PogChamp
Trindor_: yes i am renkton FrankerZ
gtnftw: skills but no money
bubblesnot: What do they win?
AshirokSC: EZ Clap
siriusb_79: FIT IN DRIP IN forsenCD
Plurmorant: LUL
numbblol: Pog
Incurs0: LUL
breadhamandegg: Pog
Heyloguys: Bronze 1 renekton LUL
Kubissus: PepeHands
Vjasal: Dab
numbblol: Yeah Pog
krystalgamer: ayyyyyy
Free3ze: LUL
Sunce_: Lurkers LUL
Plurmorant: bye brainlets
DeeboMC: I chose the wrong day (Wednesday) to go out drinking. Stayed off since then. I missed when the test was even introduced. This is the first time I’ve been back online again since. @georgehotz
pvnieo: HeyGuys
NatePh_07: LUL
TowlieGotHigh: FeelsBadMan Bye
Trindor_: vip renekton
julen9601: Can we get link of exam to watch of questions?
Warbayx: VIP Pog
EhGuyInCanada: the chat is about to become dead AF
gtnftw: Gift the first 2 a sub
DepressoMode: just mod them all
metsu_gadoken: LUL
ay420notbannedlmao: i can still speak KEKW
ConagYuirg: I'm in boys 😎
haidook: it was a pleasure chat haidoo1LUL
robinduckett: rip to all
norflin221: well i dont care, i will chat anyway
numbblol: Even if im not subscriber Kappa
miche_____: .01% of chat PogChamp
Digital_donger: do /vip their usernames PogChamp
Warbayx: You can VIP them @georgehotz
gigafact: twitch has API for you so you can make a bot George
foti_kasparov: FAK DICTATORSHIP
buzzd24: scrubs
myaocat: smart people=good people?
ZURiE: @georgehotz MOD THEM!
helofren: yea who else is never subbing again hahaha
thetimetraveler253: what is this.. CCP
i_Memberino: just type /vip
leander_ms: @B1_Renekton needs the VIP
wutango: /vip
echotaco: Note there is a limit of 100 VIPs @georgehotz
Toastie1: type /vip and name
bubblesnot: NERDS
Digital_donger: just /vip @georgehotz
internetfro9: @myaocat yes
Sunce_: do /vip then their name @georgehotz
Imeriall: WHAT WAS THE TEST?
anon543264: /vip username
foti_kasparov: You are a communist @georgehotz
gtnftw: you should have a coding competition where the winners get VIP
Mayfieldiv: I can already feel the power
LeSinographe: @thetimetraveler253 , LOL
cutza: buy it for them and then ban the rest of us, sounds fair
Warbayx: VIP USERNAME
buzzd24: can jailbreak an iphone, cant VIP on twitch
Manch___: type /vip name
leander_ms: type /vip and then the username
Den_dp: just /vip nick
Trindor_: just /vip username
Vjasal: VIP BABY PogChamp
Lintelligence: I have a legitimate reason as to why I was late to the stream and didn't take the test. Give me an all or nothing question - hit me
BossCalifornia: @georgehotz type /vip username
Digital_donger: /vip <nick>
Sunce_: @georgehotz just do "/vip username"
Vjasal: wait
TowlieGotHigh: P2W :)
krystalgamer: NOOOOOOOOO
jasonscottreval: I am not a sub
jsnfly: is he discriminating dumb people?
many_mangos: pay to win 😡
slimpimp007: shoutout to everyone who failed
localcanofdutchgold: that just means non-subs are smarter
buzzd24: IQism
thetimetraveler253: we should not tolerate this CCP-like policies
robinduckett: robinduckett is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 2 in the channel!
ay420notbannedlmao: peepee poopoo
Hypheus_: PogChamp
robinduckett: robinduckett gifted a Tier 1 sub to gogocap!
Incurs0: PogChamp
father_goats: :O
AshirokSC: PogChamp
numbblol: Im not a sub FeelsBadMan
breadhamandegg: Pog
hansgoebbels: VIP me
buzzd24: :(
matheusmota: mylonHURR mylonHURR mylonHURR mylonHURR mylonHURR keioDoisp keioDoisp keioDoisp keioDoisp mylonDab
cavad444mm: vip me
ay420notbannedlmao: not if im black
SummerChroma: vip
stalys_: FeelsBadMan i feel disciminated against
itzahmerob: VIP itzahmerob
benjamindover146: ME NEXT
Mayfieldiv: :D
gtnftw: Ashirok is VIP
ConagYuirg: georrge my name is one letter off pls change
neilsweb: If it make you guys feel better, the president of the USA would never pass this test.
gtnftw: NOICE
Trindor_: i feel attacked PepeHands
totial: what is this vip about?
hrittik166: desert me
matheusmota: mylonOK mylonOK mylonOK mylonOK mylonOK keioDoisp keioDoisp
AshirokSC: :)
totial: just arrived
thetimetraveler253: have we checked the VIP list for diversity? we need to check race and gender
this_is_falcon: why do you use mac over windows ?
myaocat: @totial can speak
jotembruv: i kinda wanna see the test i joined too late
leander_ms: nice, they are VIP that is a PogChamp
ditt0ditt0: Hi
B1_Renekton: @georgehotz lsxyzOfc
Sunce_: monkaS
Tyoo_: can /profile to check sub status
Den_dp: put /user nick
ay420notbannedlmao: scammed
gtnftw: how many subs do I have to gift to get VIP
Sunce_: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
DeeboMC: I wish I knew there had been a test to take fr
i_Memberino: you can type /user to see if they are sub
JAKWAI: he answered twice
buzzd24: LUL
matheusmota: platin55Plato platin55Plato platin55Plato platin55Plato HypeGhost HypeFrog HypeGhost HypeFrog
Incurs0: lol
spma0001: Buy vip account DM
jasonscottreval: I'm not a subscriber. It was an accident
fishpizza: will there be more tests ? I'm a new viewer and didn't know about the paper...
father_goats: ty
ditt0ditt0: I am new subscriber
avalos_02: just confused. I'm confused af LULW
benjamindover146: What was this test about?
apestreak: im on the list PogChamp
Warbayx: LUL
miche_____: LUL
tenken_sj: LUL
Free3ze: LUL
jasonscottreval: I'm not a subscriber, it was an accident
Bootstraps: @georgehotz can you link the test?
slimpimp007: looooool
riskyclix: passing grade without doing the homework
LeeFranser: LUL
Mal30: haha
many_mangos: LUL
Vjasal: Vjasal subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! @georgehotz gove me VIP
Warbayx: 1 hour LUL
DepressoMode: LUL
stalys_: gave him money.. easy VIP LUL
Locksdn: LUL
robinduckett: I gifted a sub so can you use that?
slimpimp007: LUL
neilsweb: Are we going to have more tests?
Digital_donger: he submitted every possible combination Kappa
krystalgamer: give VIP to 60%
ConagYuirg: george I spelt my name wrong on list by 1 letter
itzahmerob: Gimme VIP
Vjasal: i just did
Sunce_: D:
alexmchugh: @georgehotz MORE TESTS
ConagYuirg: pls vip me
TowlieGotHigh: D: P2W
tenken_sj: OMEGALUL
Bootstraps: Where is the test?
benjamindover146: @georgehotz What was this test about? Sorry, I missed it
totial: @myaocat :) :)
krystalgamer: @georgehotz 60% need VIP
ay420notbannedlmao: gimme aids
Trindor_: hes a sub
wutango: LUL
Sunce_: Mean FeelsBadMan
5GToren: he subbed
itzahmerob: You better have another HW
Free3ze: he subbed :D
Erick_Vertex: !uptime
ditt0ditt0: I am VIP
Mayfieldiv: george you trolled me for using Windows
father_goats: FA IR Keepo
d4rkvist3r: nice format btw 4 real
hansgoebbels: how does everyone find the time
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test?
helofren: well im a piece of shit because i dont fully understand this after starting to code 2 months ago haha
Joooooooooonas: F5 BOIS
WantRe: LUL
bubblesnot: How did i do? @georgehotz
ConagYuirg: my names spelt wromg on sheet
goobygoobler: he just subbed LUL
ConagYuirg: pls save me
Incurs0: LUL
LeeFranser: LUL
numbblol: 70% not a sub FeelsBadMan @georgehotz
Hypheus_: LUL
Sunce_: LUL LUL LUL LUL
miche_____: LUL
stalys_: LUL
jasonscottreval: I'm not a subscriber bruh. Wrote it by accident
Digital_donger: give us an autism test and we'll pass FeelsGoodMan
Lintelligence: -20 points
zimmy002: PixelBob
many_mangos: LUL
Vjasal: @georgehotz i just subbed sodaCry
ConagYuirg: i was in a rush bro
foti_kasparov: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
flaczq: vip that can't spell
Incurs0: yes
flightless_bird: NO
biniar_: There will be plenty more opportunities to make us feel stupid
solitaryyy: ban
goobygoobler: ban
stalys_: NO VIP
echotaco: @georgehotz there is a limit of 100 VIPs
breadhamandegg: NO LUL
itzahmerob: Thumbs DOWN
Sunce_: DO IT <3
kklisura: tough luck
thetimetraveler253: i feel like spelling your own name wrong is against the spirit of intelligence test
thebirdbrainer: BAN
death_gadget: ban
31337cr3w: yea
leander_ms: Just do the UNVIP and then vip the real one
Nafferza: wheres the test i would like to fail miserably
internetfro9: low iq cant spell
Free3ze: VoteYea
many_mangos: NO VIP
masters8: BAN EM
robinduckett: hahahha
BossCalifornia: VIP them
foti_kasparov: NO
NatePh_07: ban
stalys_: PERMABAN
Free3ze: BrokeBack
davidbarreroo: You should make an online test to automate this
Makouvios: BAN HIM
Mal30: BAN
ZURiE: give him VIP
internetfro9: LOW IQ CANT SPELL .
jotembruv: CANT SPELL HIS NAME= NO VIP
davidbarreroo: yeah
Trindor_: BAN HIM
Kobayawaka: BAN
ay420notbannedlmao: thats a failed question
breadhamandegg: BAN EM
NatePh_07: LUL
willarkitekt: Give him the VIP
UnnamedEntity: griZzGETGUD
chatdogy: ban
BossCalifornia: BAN
neilsweb: BAN
wutango: same name tho
robinduckett: disqualified
Sunce_: VoteYea VoteYea VoteYea
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test??
BossCalifornia: BANBAN
MEATCHOPS: no name = zERO
gtnftw: someone quick, make a Twitch account with that name
Aqualyn: FATALITY 😠
Oxynoia: ban from life
spma0001: KICIK
hjklhjklhjkl2008: can anyone link the test questions? im just curious, wasn't able to take it
aar0npham: just unvip the other guy
Sunce_: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
jsnfly: wrong answer for the name question
cutza: will you give us another test soon?
hansgoebbels: kill
ConagYuirg: woooo
aar0npham: lol
takroli3: ban him
BrodatyWhiteBear: VoteYea
tenken_sj: monkaS
ZURiE: ban anyone who missed all 10
SurfCat: LUL damn I missed the tes twhat a shame
haidook: unvip other yeah
ditt0ditt0: How to get vip, I am a subscriber
Sunce_: <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3
Lintelligence: VIP just lost its legitimacy
masters8: kill on sight
TowlieGotHigh: VoteNay
DeeboMC: He was gaming the test
benjamindover146: what was the test about?
willarkitekt: Not a spelling test
robinduckett: hahaha that was fun
itzahmerob: VIP ME
myaocat: can you vip me? im old fan :D
hawkisdead: came in too late :/
Kubissus: ok now ban the rest of us
avalos_02: What test was it? I missed it. @georgehotz
Bootstraps: @georgehotz can we get a link to the test for those of us just arriving?
TowlieGotHigh: :/
prafaeltsantos: k
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test?
Den_dp: spelling name right is hard question too Kappa
alexmchugh: @georgehotz pure intelligence test next
ay420notbannedlmao: ban us now
Sunce_: monkaS
CJslider14: this is a dope method
slimpimp007: exile gang
Warbayx: Kappa
luspr: is this a testing stream ?
5GToren: 1v1 fight bro
DeeboMC: VIP perks?
termalman: @georgehotz can you share a link to the tests?
miche_____: B1_Renekton ThankEgg
Free3ze: KappaWealth
miche_____: B1_Renekton ThankEgg B1_Renekton ThankEgg B1_Renekton ThankEgg B1_Renekton ThankEgg B1_Renekton ThankEgg B1_Renekton ThankEgg
Locksdn: the elite Kappa
MEATCHOPS: I can pay a VIP to take the test for me
thetimetraveler253: elitism
solitaryyy: whens the next test?
bubblesnot: Is the star a vip?
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test??
cybergenik: Is B1_Renekton here?
eax_ebx: TRUE LOVE
hansgoebbels: yeayyyyy
ay420notbannedlmao: banhammer
OFFICER_KKONA: @miche_____ slikPray
31337cr3w: thank you
Trindor_: whats the link
Lintelligence: when's the next text?
Mal30: @georgehotz will future tests require me to follow the contents of the stream ie. beaver knowledge?
robinduckett: Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1 Cheer1
avalos_02: Too meta LUL
Lintelligence: when is the next test?
leander_ms: Can you explain what a busy beaver even is
nat0w: Poor @Vjasal who subbed and didnt get his VIP LUL
thetimetraveler253: CCP elitism
911nash: link ?
mikey9988: richkidYep
parasite_is_a_snakee: link the test?
hawkisdead: paste url
georgehotz: https://forms.gle/2QiYgde4aMkFY9DKA
lightofhel1: that was cool
TomatoePasta: last spam FeelsGoodMan
Vjasal: @nat0w you can refund subs KEKW
bubblesnot: You should tutor the lowest 10 test takers
tenken_sj: when is next exam? Kappa
alexmchugh: @georgehotz programming test pls
ggtom: monkaS
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test?
slava_llll: URL IS DEAD SMH
ggtom: i arent click that
Locksdn: gotta follow the lore or else
buzzd24: does being a VIP here help with employment
hansgoebbels: how do you find the time to do all these lovely coding twitches and run a company ?
spma0001: ITs the Same
nat0w: @Vjasal ah LUL
cybergenik: If I knew the turing shit I would of gotten higher, god damn it.
robinduckett: twitchies
benjamindover146: URL doesn't work m8 @georgehotz
levitaete: nah click it's just a google form link
ditt0ditt0: How to be vip I am a subscriber
SurajkAxim: raerW
CJslider14: LORE or VAC
slava_llll: URL IS DEAD
ay420notbannedlmao: peepee poopoo
krystalgamer: ;(
foti_kasparov: "ALL ANIMALS ARE EQUAL, BUT SOME ANIMALS ARE MORE EQUAL THAN OTHERS"
asthmaa: it works for me
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test?
uint32t: ok I missed the test, when's the next one?
Joooooooooonas: @georgehotz do you want to make a sub icon ? the default star seems kinda boring
xDeadcain: xDeadcain subscribed with Twitch Prime.
JAKWAI: the numberphile video wasn't enough :/
Mayfieldiv: vip-only stream now?
breadhamandegg: @buzzd24 higher chance of getting into FAANG
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test??
jordandiaz1988: good job men
slava_llll: URL IS DEAD SMH
avalos_02: So it's a half iq test half cs test LUL
arbitrandomuser: when is the next one
hansgoebbels: huzzah
gigafact: you are putting so much work into the stream. well done. dont forget you pat on the back
bubblesnot: Tutor the lowest 10 test takers
myaocat: you can download chatterino and filter by vip
krystalgamer: lmfao
fizziblytwitching: You havent left in every mirror in the hall yet
5GToren: make ur own discord bro ez
hawkisdead: paste a url for the right answers
CJslider14: you can regex from a list
5GToren: in coq
fizziblytwitching: That was pretty cool
mrnivclones: I love the streams
Vjasal: don't vips can talk in subchat?
echotaco: How will you decide who get's un-VIPed when you hit the limit of 100? @georgehotz
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test?
foti_kasparov: communism
robinduckett: ScaredyCat
itzahmerob: Yes I need more tests
myaocat: https://chatterino.com/
buzzd24: what ?? LUL
itzahmerob: & HW
d4rkvist3r: just do it
NatePh_07: I am down on these tests
Dautlog: LUL
stalys_: unteachable FeelsBadMan
FargioFarmani: FeelsBadMan
ivylions: like drumline call outs
buzzd24: LMFAOOO
5GToren: hahaha
ggtom: a cult PogChamp
911nash: lol like mensa ?
JAKWAI: let them fight 1 by 1 barenuckle. The winner takes it all
bubblesnot: All jokes aside, he did a good job making the test
ay420notbannedlmao: do vips get your phone num?
CJslider14: oh man with certifications for linkedin?
benjamindover146: @georgehotz How do you determine what project you want to work on next?
marschr: VIP camgirl
Plurmorant: any crewman in chat
kaboomyoo: what kind of cult you trying to make
daxyxy98: the real clubhouse
MEATCHOPS: can i be a red shirt on the forum?
cutza: lol discord
C3r0C3r0C3r0: C3r0C3r0C3r0 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! surely people who donate large amounts of money would be also admitted
hjklhjklhjkl2008: LMAO cult of self enlightment
Bootstraps: @georgehotz you were telling us last night to review the vod of day 1 to understand busy beaver but your vods are behind a paywall. Can it be removed?
5GToren: he's gonna take up on the luminati
Plurmorant: Kappa
cro_blade: where are the answers?
Locksdn: Gentelmen club Kappa
fishpizza: Red shirt LUL
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz when is the next test??
itzahmerob: make a subreddit
SurajkAxim: raerGa i have big IQ
HEB30P0B: 4Head
lef_xyz: Kappa
Sunce_: ooooo LUL
hansgoebbels: can we have sleep overs and pillow fights also
foti_kasparov: Do VIP get access on OnlyFans
itzahmerob: and lock the subreddit
robinduckett: big brain time
masters8: Person, woman, man, camera, TV
buzzd24: i need to study tell us when it is
eddyrdqsk: Even know i cant answer any of those, it is a nice chance to learn new stuff
kachokblexinity: Глебыч, ты как здесь оказался, ЛОЛ)))
sammy_the_slayer: @bootstraps they are on youtube for free 😏
avalos_02: plutocracy WeirdChamp
TowlieGotHigh: @georgehotz Just make a discord and special rooms for VIPs :)
alexmchugh: @georgehotz VIPs vs george's 1 hour neural net
MEATCHOPS: Im gunna need a new test until i get lucky :(
levitaete: did I miss something? why do all the inputs in the test have the disabled attribute?
Bootstraps: his vods are for subs only... i can't even review them to learn
Mayfieldiv: you'll be a star camgirl soon enough with all this newfound stream effort
Joooooooooonas: @georgehotz How about a sub icon instead of the default star
HEB30P0B: @kachokblexinity bruh Kappa
thetimetraveler253: we should make a twitch bot
itzahmerob: make another test PROFESSOR
Repunk: you should check out chatterino
bangsilverfang: @georgehotz make discord?
ditt0ditt0: What is the deadline for current task
bakuldada: vip only discord
cybergenik: PepoG will this be on the test?
CJslider14: yeah regex bot from list of approved users else:
wutango: LUL
norflin221: all vots on youtube
spma0001: Has he ever cooked on his kitchen
maxpokerrr: how do i become vip
krystalgamer: smh
benjamindover146: Yo, there's a YouTube channel that archives VODs
Joooooooooonas: star != gem
leander_ms: What about actually doing something for your twitch channel
masters8: I am genius: person, woman, man, camera, TV
SurfCat: You don't need regex you can get the vip status via twitch api
kachokblexinity: HEB30P0B откуда ты узнал про этого додика?)
buzzd24: LUL
Aqualyn: 4Head
leiterLAB: no :)
norflin221: xD
ay420notbannedlmao: fuck no
ch3e3to: LUL
slava_llll: SOMEONE LINK THE PAPER
R31gnh: i dont have IG monkaS
gigafact: twitch api is amazing
myaocat: can you please the answers to review? for the python script i got 120389 but im not sure if it's correct pepoThink
TowlieGotHigh: Instagram LUL
slimpimp007: George is trying to get these if hoes
ggtom: that's 100k
norflin221: next test will be did you donate me 100$?
levitaete: that's not how instagram verification works
fishpizza: LUL
lef_xyz: u cant get VIPs from the API i think
foti_kasparov: Special video on 30k?
thetimetraveler253: george put up a better ig profile pic
pouringhotteaonyourface: raid instagram
WarSwick: HahaBall
butyesss: you can get now if you pay
asthmaa: do you post programming stuff on ig?
localcanofdutchgold: what happened to not being famous?
wholeandswole: idk man most instas I follow show a lot more skin than that LUL
chemicalflash: Post better pictures
C3r0C3r0C3r0: what's your insta? I'll follow
cutza: verified = influencer
leiterLAB: true LUL
Warbayx: LUL
lef_xyz: Kappa
bakuldada: just get on dating shows
CJslider14: welcome to the machine
maxpokerrr: make bot to dm people to follow you on ig
alexmchugh: 120389 is correct
robinduckett: Party100
5GToren: followers = p
hjklhjklhjkl2008: yea u don't buy clout, you just beg for it
Joooooooooonas: LUL
localcanofdutchgold: ok buddy Kappa
levitaete: you have to apply for and supply personal information for the verified checkmark
pouringhotteaonyourface: this is about sending the message
itzahmerob: LOL
asdhxc: coomer
breadhamandegg: LUL
robinduckett: Instagram hype
jotembruv: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 LULW
SurfCat: Seems like a quality person that girl Keepo
smurfd0: what, not improving your Brand :D
slava_llll: link to paper someone
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what if your girlfriend is watching this stream lmao
Warbayx: coomer LUL
adroniser: how tall are you bro?
TowlieGotHigh: Just hack instagram and give urself a check mark 4Head
itzahmerob: "I don't buy clout, I earn it"
masters8: COOM
masters8: LUL
pxlluu: we do :D
Fulk33: did you link your wikipedia on IG ? hahah
HopZe: coomer brain
Joooooooooonas: @georgehotz can you activate BETTER Twitch Icons ?
Warbayx: Kappa
slimpimp007: fuck boi energy in the chat
masters8: 5'3
Vjasal: don't you have a gf already? or was that your mom you were talking with?
cutza: send your Instagram to cam girls
MEATCHOPS: ' i dont buy clout, i beg for it'
robinduckett: yes play meaninglessness
kachokblexinity: I thought he was a SIMP
asdhxc: 5'10 aka 5'7"
dr_set: so your looking for groupies
SnakeOneMLG: @georgehotz open relationship with Alex?
hansgoebbels: think a big weiner works better
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz isn't alex your girlfriend?
DepressoMode: yuh
perrierking: Reminds me of Shkreli
lef_xyz: true poet
hrittik166: who's alex
Locksdn: True LUL
swsh: @georgehotz i've started watching today and got 7, last time I was here when metamath was a hype, gotta read the paper though
Warbayx: Sadge
echotaco: Being consistent across tests to maintain VIP since there are limited spots?
SnakeOneMLG: you lying
5GToren: aint nobody got time for a gf
cutza: when will you start selling your own weed bath water?
maxpokerrr: make a bot to dm people to follow you on ig
gigafact: Alex seems very complex
itzahmerob: LMAO
spma0001: Fake plastic tea
Mal30: you showed the "N word" on stream. DELETE VOD
thetimetraveler253: George can we study some physics
MEATCHOPS: All girlfriends must be VIP in chat
asdhxc: if your under 6' your a manlet
DeeboMC: Aggressive moderation today. Nice lol
this_is_falcon: why mac over windows ?
robinduckett: I hope those weren't copyrighted lyrics you were singing
Mal30: @this_is_falcon imagine having ppl finding out, that you use windows, when they see you on instragram --> no grillls
CreContent: @5gtoren NL?
SurfCat: this_is_falcon I think the question is why mac over linux Keepo
hansgoebbels: girlfriends, where we are going we dont need girlfriends
benjamindover146: Doubt this guy doesn't have a girlfriend
hrittik166: true
this_is_falcon: but windows runs games xd
hansgoebbels: to the gay bar
5GToren: @CreContent Ja
WarSwick: kp1KIT How does one fall in love with code? kp1MIL
Vjasal: i didn't do the hw and still got 70%, nice moon2M
Mal30: @this_is_falcon yep, but its incompatible with gf
SurfCat: this_is_falcon the others too but I get what you mean
kektobiologist: which github erpo is this?
this_is_falcon: o man i have been doing it all wrong
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz are you on a 13" or a 15" george ?
SurfCat: Mal30 lol
CreContent: nice naam @5gtoren
5GToren: @CreContent Thanks man😅
nikhilr14: where can I take the test?
slimpimp007: talent>hard work
that_lad_koby: Good Evening Everyone
yevenesh: @georgehotz are u only using mbp ?
sammy_the_slayer: @thomasbrah 16” one
lef_xyz: people are eager to prove themselves LUL
Thomasbrah: @sammy_the_slayer uff i like the screen realestate
CreContent: Does he have a 2nd screen?
Thomasbrah: 13 inch is a little too small for developing
Joooooooooonas: @CreContent nopoe
joaovictorsnt: llp
benjamindover146: did you really archive all of wikipedia?
sammy_the_slayer: @thomasbrah nah it’s heavy af
DeeboMC: @lef_xyz yep. Especially (most of) the type of people who follow him
hrittik166: how to learn ML on my own??
random11_real: what's the average age of your viewers?
JAKWAI: why dont u mute all non-vip's now?
Thomasbrah: @sammy_the_slayer what are you rocking ?
buzzd24: LUL
yevenesh: @Thomasbrah is he using macbookpro 13inch only?
CJslider14: talent gets you over the wall hard work gets you through it
benjamindover146: fax
Thomasbrah: @yevenesh i heard its 16inch fam
1whoknew: @georgehotz Have you ever coded on a macbook pro? And would you recommend it?
TurboWalrusTickler: 16inch late 2019
phrixus_bro: like you push through a solid walll?
sammy_the_slayer: @thomasbrah 13” one, the most recent version
butyesss: two spaces
DeeboMC: @georgehotz I don’t feel bad for them, I actually respect them
yevenesh: i hear fans, it must be 70+ degrees celcius
Thomasbrah: @sammy_the_slayer you got that esc button sick, i have the dumb touchbar wihtout esc
Twixasz: LUL
Warbayx: LUL
Baka4Life__: ZOOMER
bangsilverfang: @georgehotz If you wanna learn Penetration testing, where do you recommend to start?
OG_KNOCC_OUT: LUL
sammy_the_slayer: @thomasbrah 😆
Twixasz: lmao
hrittik166: how to learn ML on my own??
r00tkey: LUL
remegy: xD
swsh: @georgehotz Have you seen this https://writings.stephenwolfram.com/2020/06/exploring-rulial-space-the-case-of-turing-machines/ ?
myaocat: @hrittik166 i dont know ML by myself but there are many websites teach you
itzahmerob: H U H
remegy: remegy subscribed with Twitch Prime.
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @bangsilverfang ask your mom LOL
plotzera: @hrittik166 just learn it on the internet
hrittik166: ok
itzahmerob: deep lyrics George
SurfCat: hrittik166 I think I saw some stuff on it on edx
loopylol: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 LUL
iamquote: Why studying busy beavers?
KanadaCheese: what was the answer for the dogs?
theweekencl: everything is on the web literally google them
remegy: I AM SUBBED, NOW I CAN ASK DUMB QUESTIONS LIKE " HOW TO LEARN PROGRAMMING " Kappa
hrittik166: Sure I will check it out
DeeboMC: @georgehotz so is your stream now gonna be like a class where if you miss 2 days in a row, you might as well just drop the class?
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @swsh wolfram is a hack, His models are needlessly expressive and don't reveal any actual deep insights about physics
bangsilverfang: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 nice one, your a smart dude lmao
plotzera: @remegy people are so fixed on learning how to learn that they're not learning anything
xhabitsx: Check chatterino btw, you can filter messages and have VIP only showing @georgehotz
Lizardan: What vim theme he using ?
Plurmorant: pay up
levitaete: that's why it's the same price
FlashAUT_: lol
avalos_02: Kappa
FileDotJar: lmao
benjamindover146: FAX
Knarez: el
fishpizza: LUL
thetimetraveler253: george is still charging full tuition for online
Knarez: em ah oh
buzzd24: LUL
ayyyylmaooooo: Will this be on the test
j11202: will there be daily tests now lol
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @bangsilverfang just kiddin around, for pen testing i highly recommend watching liveoverflow (a channel on youtube)
phrixus_bro: harvard purveyors of truth
YouPowerRush: HahaReindeer
Witkowslon: did he went to university?
world2vec: lmao
itzahmerob: LOL
DeeboMC: @georgehotz im not here to be educated tho
Mayfieldiv: this is the first live live-stream I've caught. been going through the backlog of past streams
Locksdn: My uni's online classes are garbage
benjamindover146: Have you ever explored blockchain?
myaocat: do you miss the old days solving pwn challenges and using irc client ?
deepak_rajan_: @georgehotz what language are you coding on now? anyone?
swsh: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 Not sure, seems pretty nice foundational formalism to study physics as well as metamathematics
hrittik166: c++
JigglyGirls: anyone asked how to exit vim ? rcd5head
itsluized: @deepak_rajan_ Looks like C/C++
thetimetraveler253: @georgehotz let's design a harvard/mit replacement
SurfCat: I think that's kind of close to thetruth yeah
remegy: @georgehotz they are right ? cuz of ad revenue
itzahmerob: Good on you for ripping on Harvard
internetfro9: :)
r00tkey: So what Harvard says and we believe it?
ibimsmarry: why tho?
jordandiaz1988: How do you keep consent when you program or read?
Joooooooooonas: google scholar @georgehotz
lesserthangood: time to create Rightward
bangsilverfang: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 SeemsGood
Baka4Life__: imagine paying for education LUL
itzahmerob: Papa Johns is TRASH
Witkowslon: so he didnt study :D?
Zamachi: Can I ask you a very nooby beginner question related to constructors? Why do we use copy and move constructors, how do they work?
1whoknew: for sure
lef_xyz: its way before that
buzzd24: @ibimsmarry because its just indoctrination at this point
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @swsh read this: https://www.singlelunch.com/2020/04/23/why-stephen-wolframs-research-program-is-a-dead-end/
death_gadget: Social sciences. LUL
myaocat: So much talk about Open Source/ Open Software. Why not Open Meds? Answer: Money
dr_set: the questions is: is google part of the problem by reinforcing stupid people
Vindalis: but I want to bring my dog to work while I solve complex problems at google
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @deepak_rajan_ c++, you can tell from his file extension (.cc)
itzahmerob: I agree, they charge too much as well
EhGuyInCanada: Kappa Kappa
ayyyylmaooooo: *Colleges are evil, down with the upper class, hack the planet!*
avalos_02: @georgehotz I'm not very familiar with American universities. How are they failing?
Vindalis: the names Dade.. Dade Murphy
j11202: So are there going to be daily quizzes now?
phil4820: 5Head
gigafact: there is a poll on https://www.youtube.com/c/commaaiarchive/community about hammer if you want to check out the comments
jordandiaz1988: How do you keep consent when you program or read?
Baka4Life__: @avalos_02 1 million dollar a year for education LuL
ayyyylmaooooo: @avalos_02 they want money over actually teaching people
venatiodecorus: irc dot buttes dot com #gamme
avalos_02: Ah okay.
LEXINGTONSTEELEROBLOX: whats the point of this stream exactly?
thetimetraveler253: what would be an ideal uni system
pouringhotteaonyourface: paper link please?
Baka4Life__: @thetimetraveler253 free
lef_xyz: @LEXINGTONSTEELEROBLOX https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
localcanofdutchgold: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
itzahmerob: Well said
jordandiaz1988: How do you keep consent when you program or read?
ibimsmarry: i never understood how they are able to charge so mutch money, in germany shits free
ayyyylmaooooo: Colleges realized that teenagers were a large market of people who were untapped for their money
benjamindover146: You don't need school to learn about comp sci and related topics
Vindalis: @LEXINGTONSTEELEROBLOX to get to level 5 for autonomous self driving cars sooner
thetimetraveler253: @Baka4Life__ if it's free how do you attract the best professors
bubblesnot: @georgehotz what are some of the most interesting current PhD studies going on right now that you have seen?
1whoknew: @ibimsmarry for real, gotta love germanys eduational system tho
swsh: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 But it's not a scientific model, it's a language and a tool for studying science
levitaete: you hate on university (fair enough) but you gotta admit that in this world it's hard to get a traditional job without a degree (for us mortals)
willarkitekt: Also because Education is not a product. Good education is not what sells. Misalignment of desired outputs
myaocat: @benjamindover146 Of course not. You don't need school to learn about medicine. But are you going to do it?
fishpizza: College tuition is 1,120% higher than 1978. "CPI" inflation was only 230%
Baka4Life__: @thetimetraveler253 What do you mean the school is still the same
fishpizza: 1978-2012
Vindalis: @levitaete your github and live projects account for more in tech interviews than a degree
itzahmerob: Pizza gimme the equation for CPI
fishpizza: lol whatever the fed says it is
eldac_kno: Higher Education in Russia is free
hrittik166: #include <bits/stdc++.h> -> Anyone from the cp world
thetimetraveler253: @Baka4Life__ it's gonna cost some amount to pay professors, buy tools, pay for research, etc.
B1_Renekton: @hrittik166 wont work on mac
ditt0ditt0: I used to thought AI is the next big thing , I was very wrong
levitaete: @Vindalis yes, I'm sure that actual experience is never going to be disregarded. But I'm sure it differs from place to place
DeeboMC: @georgehotz is Rayo’s number still the biggest? Challenge chat to beat it lol
ayyyylmaooooo: levitaete I disagree, you see companies like Tesla that hire people based on if they could do the job rather than if they have a degree
fishpizza: @itzahmerob https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/CPIAUCSL
remegy: tesla lol
remegy: imagine working there
levitaete: @ayyyylmaooooo well tesla isn't a great example of the 'traditional' jobs that I was referring to, but I see your ponit
itzahmerob: @fishpizza Ty :D
macbeth420: macbeth420 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
1whoknew: @ayyyylmaooooo thats what tesla says, but idk if they really do that tho
salihyil1: napiyo suan
lightofhel1: 64
Baka4Life__: @thetimetraveler253 we just invest more money on the school instead of military or other stuff
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @swsh In science, there's a fundamental tradeoff between expressibility and interpretability. My belief aligns with the author of that article, namely that wolfram errs on the side of too much of expressibility. But as I am no expert in physics and my background is more CS theory and pure math, we are both entitled to our own opinions.
levitaete: yeah we can all agree that military spending is wack
iilliilliillli: i dont agree
Vindalis: I show prospective employers how long I've spent in this chat and I get hired straight away
benjamindover146: I think I might start streaming code like this
benjamindover146: Looks fun
ayyyylmaooooo: @vindalis ah yes, culture
thearthtyagi: @Vindalis lmao
DeeboMC: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 any thoughts on Christopher langan?
blueberryguac: i have 6k points hbu
gtnftw: I have an idea for a company that could be very successful and requires little effort
thearthtyagi: @benjamindover146 sure do it
levitaete: @iilliilliillli you don't agree that military spending (I'm talking about the US) is completely over the top and unnecessary?
joaovictorsnt: why can i speak on the chat yet ??
oqi1: hey @georgehotz this is ur mum, pls get back to folding proteins
themorph3: guys, whats todays topic ?
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @DeeboMC just googled him. Seems like a meme.
joaovictorsnt: the bound execute in steps
Baka4Life__: @levitaete how could someone not agree with this
levitaete: right
ayyyylmaooooo: @georgehotz can we get a 10 million channel point reward where you recommend us to an employer of our choosing
levitaete: @iilliilliillli https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_countries_by_military_expenditures#/media/File:Military_Expenditures_2018_SIPRI.png
DeeboMC: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 yea, but he’s quite serious and is a contentious figure because he’s actually got some valid points. Try reading his paper
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @DeeboMC I am skeptical of people who brag about their IQ instead of things that they actually accomplish. Terence Tao reportedly has the highest IQ of any living individual, but everybody knows him for his numerous contributions to math, so I am much more inclined to trust him as a source of authority.
e_s_t_i_e: @georgehotz will we have a knowledge transition in a brain in seconds like in Matrix but IRL?
B1_Renekton: @georgehotz Def 7 in paper talks about 'irrelevant'
gtnftw: @B1_Renekton type something if you can
DeeboMC: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 I agree with all those points. But Christopher Langans paper is pretty interesting
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @DeeboMC I'm highly skeptical.
OG_KNOCC_OUT: VIP can only talk in emote-only mode
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @DeeboMC What authority do you have to claim his paper is interesting. What's your background, and what specifically about his paper is interesting (rigorously)?
ditt0ditt0: Who solved the previous days tasks
DeeboMC: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 I have a brain
gtnftw: !watchtime
neilsweb: hi
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @DeeboMC Sorry, but you'll have to do better than that to convince me. Mentally challenged people also have brains.
gigafact: VIP cant talk in sub only mode
remegy: @georgehotz are you gonna do full STEM ( university ) ? or just certain subjects at first
iilliilliillli: how do you guys think you keep at bay actors like rusia if you not such a military power? keep in mind all nato is based on us military
Suspecthum: I'm still here :)
adroniser: AYY YO WHATS POPPIN GAMERS
DeeboMC: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 “to claim it’s ‘interesting?’” ... I mean... what?? Lol.. wanna reword what you’re trying to say?
bubblesnot: So we all agree the VIPs are the marching band nerds of our school?
stalys_: -430 PepeLaugh
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @DeeboMC like what gaps in the standard model of physics does it purport to address and how
Mayfieldiv: I may have been in marching band..
bubblesnot: Lol
SHAVEYY_: I switched to duckduckgo but then when I started googling computer science concepts I would only get porn
SHAVEYY_: searching*
remegy: kinda too early, but how are you gonna deal with the "pedigree" required for academic positions ? @georgehotz
hjklhjklhjkl2008: @DeeboMC what sort of insight does his cognitive-theoretic view of reality give you that mainstream science does not
ditt0ditt0: I am late to the party, guys please help 😞
remegy: busy beaver five
remegy: part 3
bubblesnot: Anyone here read sapiens?
neilsweb: So why did you pick C?
DeeboMC: @hjklhjklhjkl2008 almost out of points so this is last message until I subscribe so I’m just going to link you this. https://superscholar.org/interviews/christopher-michael-langan/
ditt0ditt0: Sapiens the book ?
hrittik166: @georgehotz Is this video going to be on youtube
AerisThor: Could halting state be special and its always +1 states ?
bubblesnot: Man its lonely at the top...can we go back to free for all chat?
ditt0ditt0: @hrittik166 yeah that will be on YouTube
lemmywemmy: good morning chat :)
1v3ease: i am late, did we do the test?
neilsweb: @1v3ease Ya.
gigafact: @1v3ease you can take it https://forms.gle/2QiYgde4aMkFY9DKA
reubenpig: reubenpig subscribed at Tier 1.
1v3ease: @neilsweb thanks
clinuco: clinuco subscribed with Twitch Prime.
ericvaneri9k: ericvaneri9k subscribed at Tier 1.
bubblesnot: Welcome to the inner circle boys
ericvaneri9k: what is this your doing @georgehotz
gigafact: @ericvaneri9k is this https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
ditt0ditt0: I am still studying TMs, can’t understand these 😅
KryekGG: 80/20 rule
ericvaneri9k: what do you with this?
remegy: green T for the busy B
remegy: its not practical, just for fun
remegy: @ericvaneri9k
ericvaneri9k: got it
ericvaneri9k: thnks
dorkmo: change your locks now
dorkmo: change your locks
Ziv0: wtf LUL
dorkmo: change yoru locks
solitaryyy: $4,000
gigafact: But why, some say, the Moon? Why choose this as our goal? And they may well ask, why climb the highest mountain? Why, 35 years ago, fly the Atlantic? Why does Rice play Texas?
remegy: YOURE GETTING RAIDED
SmokeSomethin: you're virginity
SmokeSomethin: Keepo
SHAVEYY_: the FBI is shutting Geo down again
jordandiaz1988: How do you keep consent when you program or read?
ditt0ditt0: FBI
willarkitekt: Nice guy checking you are ok
ditt0ditt0: Sony
SkywardDev: Was he wearing a mask?
bubblesnot: Wtf
remegy: he probs works for Google they been watching your stream
TusKaN_BaNaNas: Just because you're paranoid doesn't mean they aren't really out to get you
ditt0ditt0: It was coronavirus who came.
Mayfieldiv: he needed those 9v smoke detector batteries
bubblesnot: You aught to get a ring for interior of your unit...
remegy: George is defo a Libra
bubblesnot: Was that Elon trying to steal your source code?
remegy: whats elon gonna do with it, he only knows LAMP
bubblesnot: Touché
gigafact: how many points you guys have? I am at almost 20k
ditt0ditt0: Anyone here pro coder ?
iilliilliillli: whoever gave me this https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_countries_by_military_expenditures#/media/File:Military_Expenditures_2018_SIPRI.png is an idiot, check the % to gdp chart. Who uses nominal values???????
Bootstraps: https://clips.twitch.tv/TangibleWrongUdonFloof
deadpool_reynolds: YES, we are free
SolarBerry: FREEDOM!!
YouPowerRush: HahaReindeer
itzahmerob: IM FREE
TooManyBytes: freedom
ronLno: FREEEEEEEEEEE
BossCalifornia: Hello gamers
iofault: AngelThump
avalos_02: monkaS
localcanofdutchgold: the na way lul
Styler: elementsS
21_savior: xqcS
oqi1: finally
Nafferza: Pog
nesbylol: what are we doing today?
oqi1: CTC
marink031: is there a clip or command that explains what is busy beaver five?
more_or_less_or: Do you think that A.I. researchers have not taken into account the presence of neurotransmitters enough?
nizero: george are u staying east coast for awhile ?
carlwinsl0w95: ill still be here for part 100
that_lad_koby: Hi
NewLifeStartsNOW: what if I was fapping and that superviser guy came in? wtf
ditt0ditt0: You are my inspiration
deadpool_reynolds: FBI Open UP... oh we are late now
bubblesnot: Welcome back!
oqi1: BatChest BatChest
bubblesnot: It was getting lonely at the top boys
itzahmerob: Supervisor guy called him from a NJ # and he ignored it LOL
extrathiccboiiii: huskPog
slev0182: can u hack humanity back in time to before 2020?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: why are we coding in c and not python?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: tought c was garbage
MrStereoX: @georgehotz Are you still working on the corona project ? :)
itzahmerob: Bc
NewLifeStartsNOW: do you think George read book on programming? which is good
marink031: what made you think c is garbage xD
marink031: I'm assuming that was sarcasm
sonunakadaraytmoruqqq: HEY GEORGE HOTZ YOU ARE MY HERO
adroniser: johnny its about the best tool for the task. STAY MAD BRO
flansel: this is c++ though
levitaete: ye
bubblesnot: @newlifestartsnow he probably heard George hammering his keys and thought he was fappining
extrathiccboiiii: I have 0 coding knowledge, but somehow enjoy thisd
NewLifeStartsNOW: @bubblesnot LUL
oqi1: we need to fold proteins and solve anti-ageing bro
NewLifeStartsNOW: I don't like programming
gregcantcode: all those angry keystrokes making me really enjoy my mouse.
oqi1: i mean ageing
TusKaN_BaNaNas: To whoever posted that Christopher Langen thing, that dudes wack af
NewLifeStartsNOW: but I can do it
ronLno: NotLikeThis
gigafact: it's lightning fast that's why @JohnnyThe_Hobo
adroniser: chris langan's paper is complete nonsense
slev0182: thats life, easy to do wrong hard to do right lol
NewLifeStartsNOW: learned 2 years at master degree. didn't liked
remegy: yo we could like, if we had to, we could actually like hack the server like for google and stuff and get all the like good juice
NewLifeStartsNOW: this guy just do it for fun?
remegy: ye bro
remegy: he knows it
remegy: and its fun once you know it
aj37z: nested for loops PepeLaugh
aj37z: O(n^3)
himusta: what are we doing today
adroniser: Are yall gonna get chips in your brains
levitaete: yes
TusKaN_BaNaNas: Do you think george could train us a neural net linter?
marink031: Can anybody from chat whisper me what is he doing and what is Busy beaver five?
ForsakenReborn: holy the chat today is aids
bubblesnot: Already have the reader rabbit chip in my brain
NewLifeStartsNOW: I can't sleep afterr long day of coding. brain is too overloaded 4Head
HawkMonk: wtf is this chat
oqi1: goddamn nerds NotLikeThis
levitaete: I blame newlife
adroniser: Just ignore chat its always shit
barcoga: YEP
aj37z: coding is just language translator stop overcomplicating it
Digital_donger: YEP
remegy: nice one bro
remegy: nice
NewLifeStartsNOW: @aj37z DansGame
lef_xyz: this chat is DansGame
TJSparks: DansGame NO YOU
itsChopsticks: watching this stream makes me wish i wasn't so bad at maths.
aj37z: yes programming just another word for "Translator"
aj37z: how about that
NewLifeStartsNOW: @aj37z its simple like writing with a pen? 4Head
Digital_donger: maybe he needs separate sub/vip and pleb chat
bubblesnot: Symb0ls
JohnnyThe_Hobo: idk whats going on tbh
flansel: and human is just another word for collection of atoms... technically right but it misses the point
levitaete: thank you
m1sh3ruu: 😊
bubblesnot: Is this html?
levitaete: yeah he's programming some htmls
aj37z: look hes translating pdf text into code machine langauge
Digital_donger: @bubblesnot yes he's going to add a marquee
barcoga: 4Head
bubblesnot: He should his font
oqi1: hes finally becoming a frontender, nice
levitaete: <strong>boy
aj37z: CSS though..... is very complicated
ToxyViper: why not += 1 or ++1? KomodoHype KomodoHype
Mayfieldiv: once you're generating at least all the relevant machines, you can filter out some more based on blank tape condition (def 7)
iexplorespace: not enough type coercion to be front-end Kappa
burntwilly: Needs more <blink>
NewLifeStartsNOW: @aj37z how to automate it? we need software that does that, not human
aj37z: CSS difficulty > AI difficulty
rakeshmane: xD
JohnnyThe_Hobo: 9 PogChamp
itzahmerob: Good shit George
JohnnyThe_Hobo: we need more machines
bubblesnot: Wordpress > ai
TheAwesomePaul: What is he doing
levitaete: I feel like @aj37z is trolling because everything he's said in the past 10 minutes makes me want to not live
TJSparks: wow so smart
domaxl0l: we rich baby
nesbylol: nice
MyntiMix: whats he coding?
iilliilliillli: this dude
icaroicaroicaro_: whats happening?
nesbylol: @MyntiMix busy beaver
SolarBerry: CSS is the worst thing ever created
m1sh3ruu: TPFufun
gigafact: that took like 7 hours? to get to this point?
oqi1: TheIlluminati
remegy: front end > back end
levitaete: @SolarBerry how would you do what css does in an easier way?
nickname6031: what OS is this?
mashafique: Hey all elaHi
NewLifeStartsNOW: does we have other coding channels at twitch?
remegy: its the one you pay big money for
TheAwesomePaul: Why is he using Java?
Digital_donger: @nickname6031 it's a mac
localcanofdutchgold: java lul
ToxyViper: could someone say what's different with += or ++1 and why he's use = n+1? HahaSweat
pz3300: Sup George?
bubblesnot: Why does one have _ _ _?
levitaete: it's not java it's lua
SolarBerry: @levitaete i'm a game developer so i would do it with materials and scene graphs lol
TheAwesomePaul: wait its not java? Oh ok
Mayfieldiv: good time to commit and push
localcanofdutchgold: it's obviously javascript dudes
TusKaN_BaNaNas: george is attempting to find the largest number of 1 written to the tape by a terminating turing machine of a set number of states and symbols
AdamIsSoPro: what exactly are you doing George?
brotas_: @SolarBerry how is that easier LUL
gregcantcode: that's what he said. Java.
Surfboard: ow
oqi1: DansGame
Poohcan: it's not java it's haskell
levitaete: it's not java! he's programming in matlab
ImNotTrolling: can anyone link the pdf
oqi1: thought thats vim
localcanofdutchgold: no, javascript is the assembly of the web
bubblesnot: Guys this is cobol
TusKaN_BaNaNas: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
burntwilly: headphone warning
Just_GR: What is going on with the mic today
remegy: my mans got 666 viewers
Mayfieldiv: you can filter out some more based on blank tape condition (def 7)
Jannnik: its clearly vimscript
SolarBerry: @brotas_ because i'm biased :^)
HurricaneFP: can we get our hands on the code?
gigafact: What is the first thing It comes to your mind when you hear *Turing machine*?
remegy: its on github
itsmemariobnba: nah this is clearly plain english
world2vec: @georgehotz what's your opinion on UFOs? apparently Pentagon is seriously studying them?!
bubblesnot: @mayfieldiv why does it fill some of them in with _ _ _?
brazen_bu11: i heard this channel drops some java tutorial, i cant wait to learn !!
CazoDK: What language? C++? C?
grekler3: English
2_am: hi @chat & @georgehotz
felperahn: c++
gregcantcode: it's clearly cobol
oqi1: id like to learn mergesort in holyc
CazoDK: scratch
gigafact: @HurricaneFP https://github.com/geohot/twitchcoq/tree/master/bb
Elinbae: @georgehotz did you go to any university to get this savant-level good or are you self taught?
Mayfieldiv: blank tape condition is part of a machine being relevant
TusKaN_BaNaNas: do it in x86 assembly first
NewLifeStartsNOW: @world2vec they stopped foundation
grekler3: D:
remegy: university education CoolStoryBob
oqi1: SeemsGood
AdamIsSoPro: what is this project for?
NewLifeStartsNOW: @AdamIsSoPro for stream CoolStoryBob
remegy: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Busy_beaver
TusKaN_BaNaNas: gotta find if shit halts bro
pz3300: “He’s on about the birds now, what have the birds ever done to you”. Life of brian
AdamIsSoPro: LUL
world2vec: @NewLifeStartsNOW yeah but USNavy will release stuff "not of this planet" wtf https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/23/us/politics/pentagon-ufo-harry-reid-navy.html
bradyry773: WOW - first stream i've actually made live!
remegy: yo follow him on instagram
askii23: !help
bradyry773: NICE BEAVER
Mayfieldiv: My name's Mayfield. the "iv" is "the fourth"
Mayfieldiv: you trolled me with windows
buttez: "copy_paste_go_brrrrr" LUL
ahahaitslit: instagram is for plebs
fennB612: are we trying to beat the 5,2 record?
Elinbae: i agree, its all about tiktok nowadays
NewLifeStartsNOW: @world2vec cool
remegy: ayeee my man knows
remegy: tiktok is getting banned
remegy: all dem kids who are millionaires are gonna cry like crazy
Elinbae: doubt
ahahaitslit: it was banned in india
Mayfieldiv: @fennB612 yes or, more probably, prove the currently known max by exhausting all possibilities
itzahmerob: when you build a career on a shitty platform that happens @remegy
remegy: wdym bro
remegy: they're crazy smart ( if you want money )
remegy: they like 10 and make bank
bradyry773: tiktok has crazy reach even when you post complete nonsense content
remegy: I dont think anyone in this chat was 10 and made bank
remegy: calling them stupid is kinda crazy
Mayfieldiv: tape could alternatively keep track of how many 1's are set (or non-zeros)
itsmemariobnba: percentage of chat which actually knows what's going on?
Zakcha1: hi what is this do u think ur smart or something lol...
TheAwesomePaul: not me :)
levitaete: 0%
oqi1: das too much
TJSparks: WutFace what is that sound
TusKaN_BaNaNas: just mayfielddiv
lunchbag37: someday..
bubblesnot: I like to take naps during George’s stream, it makes me feel like the old high school days of sleeping in class
JohnnyThe_Hobo: @itsmemariobnba im here for the key-board sound tbh
ahahaitslit: I'm a cs student who just watches to read about some new things, not follow 100%
Elinbae: i just found out he did not attend any respectable university, anything he does from this point onwards is irrelevant
buttez: I'm here for the scuffed audio pops
ahahaitslit: i assume many here are doing something similar
levitaete: I think you're right
ced0xF: Use Haskell with LogicT library for non-determinism
polymeris: Maybe thats why is done in Prolog, nondeterminism
mashafique: @Elinbae LUL That's a pretty limited way of thinking.
Mayfieldiv: is_blank should check for 0's instead of 1's to support more symbols (not helpful for the current situation)
EhGuyInCanada: HeyGuys
bradyry773: flask or django come at me
notice_me_OpieOP: sup chat? RonSmug /
m1sh3ruu: さよなら Georgie! laters! 😉 KonCha
TusKaN_BaNaNas: @bradyry773 depends
TusKaN_BaNaNas: obvs
topbxy: hire Mayfield already
nizero: george the universe is just a Busy Beaver program running on an extra-dimensional supercomputer and the higher-ups don't know whether or not it will halt yet.
EdwardApollo: George: When is the Honda Torque mod stream
EdwardApollo: LUL
spma0001: do someone knows what is he doing
EdwardApollo: Also, what are we working on today
31337cr3w: hes taking over the world
JohnnyThe_Hobo: we are chasing a busy beaver
bradyry773: beavers!
Elinbae: will he actually accomplish anything by doing this successfully?
Elinbae: might be a good idea to use your time on something constructive
JohnnyThe_Hobo: ofc, he'll catch the beavers
3rdeyer: a portal will open once he finishes
itzahmerob: Lmao
Klezk: ^_^ /
gigafact: @Elinbae you talk while you waste your time on twitch. well done
TusKaN_BaNaNas: Its math clout chasing
anguscupcake: the beavers will come through the portal
Elinbae: @gigafact this wasnt about me bruv
gregcantcode: we are the beavers
onelivesleft: is that "for int d : {" syntax normal c++?
session_variable: how we doin boys
remegy: yo @Elinbae he just does it for his own pleasure, the same way we play games or watch twitch. Some other people do this shit for fun, you cant always expect to do everything with a "productive " purpose, sometimes you gotta just chill around
Elinbae: @remegy i disagree, anything you do should be productive
remegy: why ?
Baka4Life__: @Elinbae Yikes
itzahmerob: Bc
mashafique: elaYIKES Yikers
Elinbae: socialism, mostly
Baka4Life__: learn to have fun
sparrow_47: It's producing fun
gregcantcode: who let the PM in here?
polymeris: Like if "productive" was objective, maybe the only way to define productiveness is with busy beavers
gigafact: you must be fun at parties @Elinbae
anguscupcake: productivity is a scam
ForsakenReborn: apart from having fun he is also learning new stuff ape
localcanofdutchgold: @Elinbae chill out bruh
Elinbae: probably not, but im productive
alystairplays: !project
anantacodes: Commenting is more productive than working on a paper. Omegalul
remegy: you probs watched some elon musk video that told you he works "100 hours a week "
onelivesleft: watching twitch is productive...
itzahmerob: Fair
alystairplays: What's busy beaver?
mashafique: @remegy LUL
TusKaN_BaNaNas: but I mean if he did find a longer outputting machine for 5 states and 2 symbols that would be some real shit
sparrow_47: LOL this kid is a pro troll. Got this whole chat worked up
notice_me_OpieOP: sup chat? RonSmug /
Elinbae: Kappa
alystairplays: there's no !project so I have no idea what I'm looking at :S
itzahmerob: LUL
Digital_donger: @alystairplays math game https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Busy_beaver
topbxy: TriHard
anantacodes: Shall we run a campaign against the troll now?
localcanofdutchgold: @sparrow_47 he's a productive troll
session_variable: that's it
session_variable: sub only chat
mashafique: @anguscupcake I like that though. "Productivity is a scam."
Elinbae: yes
Elinbae: do it, i'll sub
sparrow_47: I had a feeling that would happen - boo!
anantacodes: Make Elin Sub Campaign
alystairplays: @Digital_donger this... this is way beyond me :(
session_variable: the focus on productivity is the problem not productivity itself
itsmemariobnba: where can i find the paper?
Digital_donger: @alystairplays same. I failed the test
TusKaN_BaNaNas: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
session_variable: just because you're productive doesn't make it bad
itsmemariobnba: tyty
gregcantcode: https://youtu.be/CE8UhcyJS0I nice vid explaining what's up
fissen: codinggCode codinggWAOUW
cocovert1: I dont know programming but i'm still enjoying this
Elinbae: i bet any random google employee would solve this within minutes
TJSparks: @Elinbae ????
imamazing87: what paper is this ^^
visheshsinha: I dont think so @Elinbae
Digital_donger: @Elinbae top tier trollling PogChamp
levitaete: google employees aren't magic
Poohcan: where is the test?
Elinbae: i dunno, its pretty hard to get a job at google, i'd say these are the type of entry tests they do
visheshsinha: @imamazing87 https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
nizero: busy beaver is a turing machine that goes super expotential in computation, it goes into infinite recursion trying to find a halt state
knead_too_when: veldLA
Chronark: Based on the API-s Google provide, their developers are average at best.
nizero: hence the universe is a busy beaver program looking for a halt state
imamazing87: @visheshsinha thanks
Elinbae: average doesnt make that much money, duh
nizero: george is trying to break out of the program
Chronark: Ok, you're trolling, lo.
smakatak: am I only one who dont get this ??
notice_me_OpieOP: sup chat? RonSmug /
aj37z: eth is mooning
Mayfieldiv: that sounds right
3rdeyer: @smakatak yes
gabrielopesantos: @notice_me_OpieOP OpieOP
death_gadget: The only time that the tape can be blank is in the initial state
Elinbae: wouldnt call 1.27% mooning tho
notice_me_OpieOP: @gabrielopesantos OpieOP /
death_gadget: *allowed
limitedbyinfinity: why not asking gpt3
Iliftmymousealot: did anybody read the paper?
polymeris: I think it would be interesting to see what "busy beavers" an be made with other formalisms of computation, not just Turing Machines and its many variants.
itsmemariobnba: did he check the author's source code bedfore starting?
TusKaN_BaNaNas: no i dont think so
polymeris: He did
NicosPops: Yo hotzzz
TusKaN_BaNaNas: oh nvm then
Iliftmymousealot: what are the test questions?
litesam: Gist of what he is doing?
Mayfieldiv: maybe they output once they know it's irrelevant so you can compare subsequently generated machines to the known-irrelevant ones?
ivche1337: what are we writing?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: i didnt understood a word from that
iilliilliillli: when is the test?
3rdeyer: the test starts in 15 minutes
Iliftmymousealot: i think we are computing a turing machine
ivche1337: oh
Iliftmymousealot: tf.push() gave it away
TusKaN_BaNaNas: @iilliilliillli sorry you slept through ur midterm broh, gonna have to retake the class next semester
Andro_Bit: i like his struggle faces he looks like hes gonna explode
iilliilliillli: effffff dude
Mayfieldiv: oh from the paper "we have chosen to retain such machines in order to simplify the definition of the generation process"
TJSparks: delete everything and restart untill it works
anguscupcake: I dropped out, too much work
death_gadget: What's more likely at this point a flaw in your logic, or a bug in the code?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: what if the paper is wrong
MrBankster: are you still skeptical of masks? im still not sure about them
joaovictorsnt: what color scheme ??
Drulik1099: Did you thought about teaching pc programming?
Andro_Bit: is that a giant microwave
Iliftmymousealot: teaching pc programming kinda backspace.ao
visheshsinha: Yea Giant Microwave
Iliftmymousealot: "backspace.ai"
dreameragar33: in plain english, what is he doing?
DRIED_COW_FETUS: suh dude can you give an explanation about what you are doing for the more smooth brained gentleman
Lakimadscientist: he types so angrily
anguscupcake: just Wikipedia it brah
dreameragar33: i did , and i got a busy beaver song
notice_me_OpieOP: solving the busy beaver problem takes almost as long as trying to center a div with css
Waywoah: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Busy_beaver
offtheband: hi there, what are you working on today?
anguscupcake: CSS is worse by far
offtheband: i like it when someone code from research paper
solotope: something something cellular automata computational reducibility
solotope: geohot is the 2nd law of thermodynamics true or bs?
offtheband: lol @thE_j2o wat?
lauralex98: Stephen Wolfram here? ahahah
visheshsinha: PogChamp
cnovacost: Good afternoon/morning/night
solotope: fuckin knew it
session_variable: makes too much sense
solotope: ha ha ha
Bootstraps: LUL
Iliftmymousealot: finally a website without a call to action
Iliftmymousealot: praise
St47ik: hello there HeyGuys
world2vec: what's the purpose of this busy beaver? what can we do with it?
world2vec: too smooth brain to understand
Mayfieldiv: 1RB 2LB 1RH 2LA 2RB 1LB
anguscupcake: nothing
Mayfieldiv: http://www.logique.jussieu.fr/~michel/ha.html
jisaku: sorry guys i'm late, can someone link me the quiz
Iliftmymousealot: In addition to posing a rather challenging mathematical game, the busy beaver functions offer an entirely new approach to solving pure mathematics problems. Many open problems in mathematics could in theory, but not in practice, be solved in a systematic way given the value of S(n) for a sufficiently large n.[11
Poohcan: need hammer
pedruuz: whats going on here?
localcanofdutchgold: he's brain juicing
trump4200000: What a you're opinion on lucky palmer
JohnnyThe_Hobo: busy beaver competition? These people are professional busy beaver catchers, wtf
smurfd0: have you seen these implementations? https://github.com/pkrumins/busy-beaver
session_variable: nice
JohnnyThe_Hobo: geo hacked the paper PogChamp
session_variable: that one has python and c++
Mayfieldiv: lol
marschr: dem inductionzz
TJSparks: so its 0 thru L+1 ?
Deni1111: in the old days they used "rtfm"
TheKoreanZombi: We off by one boys.
Deni1111: so what is happening
Mayfieldiv: I like this collection of machines better. Kind of dumb they were adding irrelevant machines to run
Mayfieldiv: not adding the irrelevant ones to "out"
inittowinit: what is the purpose of this code?
devbot6: get outta SD before the big earthquake my friend
randslc: @georgehotz are you streaming from a macbook?
trump4200000: PartyTime
trump4200000: DxCat
Bogz75: CTC
Aecxlol: Bonjour
trump4200000: PartyTime
drbroms: watching this video i'm feeling again like a junior developer tituscPalm
Aecxlol: PartyTime
trump4200000: PartyTime
LiveCustoms: your pc bout to explode?
trump4200000: epic
itzahmerob: Lmao
Aecxlol: PartyTime
devbot6: Bezos secretly got your meta data tapped lol
itzahmerob: Fans taking off
trump4200000: PartyTime
Iliftmymousealot: get to the chopper
LiveCustoms: I've never heard a Mac that loud before lmao
trump4200000: release Obamas emails
Aecxlol: PartyTime
session_variable: you could rewrite it in lisp
trump4200000: c+
devbot6: create a parser to retrieve hillarys emails
trump4200000: PartyTime
Iliftmymousealot: water cooling inc
angusmiguel: did he got his DNA code yet?
joaovictorsnt: water cooling is working hard
Aecxlol: PartyTime
BobbyFlo: hey im just here to let you know i didnt read the paper
mehmet_abicim: excited about the New ps5?
Internetuse: too many print statements
trump4200000: PartyTime
Mayfieldiv: could always turn 0-dextrous check back on
Aecxlol: PartyTime
trump4200000: @bobbyflo lol
dreameragar33: @Mayfieldiv u a programmer too?
session_variable: is this code on github yet?
devbot6: Bezos would love your meta data
FargioFarmani: so many VIPs today here
session_variable: nice
Joooooooooonas: @FargioFarmani he made them vip after passing the test
Mayfieldiv: @dreameragar33 yep
dreameragar33: sick
dreameragar33: yall are crazy tbh , this is so much work
trump4200000: who got the SB dunk low pros today
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: NotLikeThis stop printing to stdout
keenxyz: what is george currently doing?
astrocraft23: hi
Iliftmymousealot: so there was a test?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: now we are chasing ducks too? PogChamp
trump4200000: PartyTime
devbot6: Bezos
dreameragar33: @Mayfieldiv how hard is it what he is doing rn?
Internetuse: any more search engine builder streams ?
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: @georgehotz u could spin up some pthreads
devbot6: Bezos needs your meta
Mayfieldiv: back to your "spawn a thread" idea
Iliftmymousealot: well it is an unsolved mathematical/computer science problem so I guess pretty hard? But I think you are trolling
JohnnyThe_Hobo: @dreameragar33 this is that kind of stuff where people spend half their life on
xxtrippyhippyxx_: yes
bradyry773: yess
BobbyFlo: yes
xxtrippyhippyxx_: ,ulti thread it
trump4200000: PartyTime
Joooooooooonas: Yes
TJSparks: its easy to write for loop multi threaded
0xDBF00: -j16 goes brrrrr
dreameragar33: @JohnnyThe_Hobo u mean what he is working on right now or being a programmer in general?
Aecxlol: PartyTime
Joooooooooonas: If you want to do it on bigger scale you have to
JohnnyThe_Hobo: @dreameragar33 this project
devbot6: We should hack sony into a lawsuit again
dreameragar33: @JohnnyThe_Hobo whats the end of it supposed to be?
trump4200000: hack the PS5
dreameragar33: @JohnnyThe_Hobo can he make it?
PutYourMoneyOnMe: Don't print most of the progress, just some fraction of iterations (i % something == 0)
devbot6: Did mr gates ever pay you for that sony hack
JohnnyThe_Hobo: @dreameragar33 idk whats the end but we are here to find out if he can make it
dreameragar33: @JohnnyThe_Hobo cool
ced0xF: the end is just a number
dreameragar33: so this hasnt been solved before?
devbot6: Did mr gates ever pay you for that sony hack
ced0xF: no its an open problem in theoretical computer science
32bitrobo: what is he doing?
dreameragar33: @ced0xF i see
bradyry773: he's beavering
BobbyFlo: im going to try to write this in procedural php
JediPotatoPotato: poor macbook gunna get WORKED today
blizzyshah: Hey can you do hackthebox or CTF soon
ikiwixz: @georgehotz did you try g++ -O3 ?
bradyry773: wheres the ice tea?
trump4200000: MacBook pro baby! - Jeb Bush
j0ca1995: @georgehotz who inspire you?
visheshsinha: Is that air conditioner in background ? Or his Mac is heating up
blizzyshah: Can you do CTF one day
trump4200000: @j0ca1995 lucky palmer
blizzyshah: @georgehotz hey
TJSparks: program go brrrrr
bradyry773: @j0ca1995 dwayne the rock johnson
BobbyFlo: @georgehotz yo whats the cheapest car I can get that works with autopilot? if you know if off the top of your head
trump4200000: @bobbyflo get a TSLA
32bitrobo: @trump4200000 anduril industries is actually pretty good
BobbyFlo: @trump4200000 true what am i thinking
Mayfieldiv: how many machines does each starting machine generate? if it's pretty evenly distributed, could do each independently on different thread
session_variable: what's a mutex
ikiwixz: just use a mutex
Bretel: PThread library
leonostjen: what is he doing?
ced0xF: we need beavering@home, everyone pools their compute power to solve bb(5)
ravicat: don't tell me guys LUL 668 of you got the 10 questions right?
invertedgold: there's a single-header file lib thread.h that has a standard queue in it
chemicalflash: OpenMP ?
ikiwixz: dont write it just use it
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: stl includes a mutex i think
JdPaulBlart: maybe 1.5 seconds is ok
ravicat: yes it does
trump4200000: we need a C++ sound cloud rapper
trump4200000: PartyTime
chatdogy: import mutex
TowlieGotHigh: i mean, u got 5 VIPs today, make them do it? KEKW
ravicat: C++11 gave us mutex
JohnnyThe_Hobo: LUL
j0ca1995: what language is he using?
ravicat: C
ravicat: C++
invertedgold: Good lib for this: https://github.com/mattiasgustavsson/libs/blob/main/thread.h
solotope: TSMC coming out with the beaver ASIC i heard
JdPaulBlart: this is a language called scala
session_variable: oh its a lock
OFFICER_KKONA: @georgehotz why not use std::lock_guard?
chemicalflash: try OpenMP
GandalfTheGrayOfHell: FeelsBadMan no multithreading
trump4200000: optimize it
JediPotatoPotato: try doing a barrel roll @georgehotz Kappa
videogamer123: im new what program is he making rn
EhGuyInCanada: busy beaver 5
trump4200000: @videogamer123 hello Jeff bezos
JediPotatoPotato: @videogamer123 google the title
ahahaitslit: just google busy beaver
Mayfieldiv: how many machines does each starting machine generate? if it's pretty evenly distributed, could do each generation tree independently on a thread with its own priority queue
PutYourMoneyOnMe: just rewrite it all in node js, using leftpad.io
joaovictorsnt: save Brazil
mmohssin: Do you have any stream schedule?
dreameragar33: he is a programmer
dreameragar33: he doesn
nudax: i like the writing speed
JdPaulBlart: no he is not a programmer
OFFICER_KKONA: @georgehotz use lambdas, it's easier
bradyry773: std::atomic
TJSparks: std?
PutYourMoneyOnMe: use pthreads , less nonsense
RunnerMD: @georgehotz how are you?
RunnerMD: hi from Moldova
OFFICER_KKONA: try with emplace_back maybe?
TJSparks: g++ -pthread
GABRIIIIIIIELL: where i can find the paper?
bradyry773: is this so they run concurrently?
JdPaulBlart: -lpthread or something
yunta2k2020: Hello from Argentina !!!
Redpsychic: is the generate func correct form?
visheshsinha: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf @GABRIIIIIIIELL
joaovictorsnt: -pthread
TJSparks: try a test void function
GABRIIIIIIIELL: @visheshsinha ty so much
JdPaulBlart: your missing the flag
OFFICER_KKONA: pass as function pointer, maybe?
JdPaulBlart: youre
chemicalflash: -lpthread maybe (with an "l")
gigafact: this paper is spreading like wildfire
bradyry773: My boy george here computing the uncomputable
OFFICER_KKONA: Ah, i see kek
smilemrpunk2: The import ?
TJSparks: lol
u3mur4: std::generate ?:DD
JdPaulBlart: im going to get bjorne on the phone
Mayfieldiv: oh boy c++..
GABRIIIIIIIELL: he code like hollywood movies thinks ppl code
TheKoreanZombi: generate is reserved?
beastialiity: This looks complex
PutYourMoneyOnMe: jesus christ
aj37z: his fingers are electric
Lefer_: @GABRIIIIIIIELL Yea coding in terminal with tmux looks badass LUL
OFFICER_KKONA: inb4 deadlock monkaS
err_ctx: that's why you don't "using std;"
TJSparks: monkaS memory leak
leander_ms: Oh are we doing actual coding today? Like with the terminal? That is so exciting, teach me George what do you do?
gigafact: @Lefer_ this terminal is fancy
bubblesnot: @georgehotz what do you have so far?
Mayfieldiv: try with smaller M/N
bradyry773: what the hell is the difference between quintuple and quadruple?#
bradyry773: big brain time
Poohcan: 1
Joooooooooonas: well LUL
bubblesnot: @bradyry773 lol wasn’t that in like the first paragraph? It shook me too
TJSparks: what?
thetimetraveler253: hue hue hue
YouPowerRush: HahaReindeer ?
nudax: :D
Elinbae: he productive now?
Mayfieldiv: and that's what RAII is for
NatePh_07: deadlock LUL
OFFICER_KKONA: @georgehotz use lock guards so you dont have to lock and unlock manually all the time
trump4200000: PartyTime
chowzor: Hi George..I have the dumb..how 2 fix? My job is going to figure it out soon..i can't trick them into thinking I don't have the dumb forever.
TJSparks: @georgehotz memory leak in line 273 monkaS
gigafact: bad code makes it slower
trump4200000: SCAM!
NatePh_07: maybe overhead is too big for small number of threads?
trump4200000: PartyTime
Mayfieldiv: too much contention for lock
TJSparks: i was always told multithreading is always faster Kappa
JdPaulBlart: multi threading is for professionals only
bradyry773: Alan turing was an absolute genius
im_bat_boy: When is question time ?
pwnbase: Some people, when confronted with a problem, think “I know, I’ll use multithreading”. Nothhw tpe yawrve o oblems.
Redpsychic: depends on implementation I guess?
Mayfieldiv: could call generate on each thread for each starting machine with its own priority queue. no contention there
jisaku: there is a generate in <algorithm>
Tapeda: like asmr those taps
bradyry773: ICE TEA!
EhGuyInCanada: deez nuts
nudax: hes not at home?
bradyry773: whats he coming back with boys
cengea: SSSsss
bradyry773: money on ice tea
EhGuyInCanada: can someone please gift me with a sub?
TJSparks: download more RAM = faster
bradyry773: damn
gigafact: @EhGuyInCanada you have prime
EhGuyInCanada: @gigafact can i use prime to subscribe?
TJSparks: yes
EhGuyInCanada: i guess i have it from amazon
EhGuyInCanada: how do i do that?
Joooooooooonas: @EhGuyInCanada Click on Subscribe an then with prime
im_bat_boy: !uptime
EhGuyInCanada: if i subscribe with prime here, can i still use it on other channels? or is it only one?
TJSparks: only one use
Joooooooooonas: @EhGuyInCanada 1 only per month
EhGuyInCanada: oh dang
gigafact: it's worth it on George
TJSparks: don't give money to rich people
EhGuyInCanada: does it renew on august 1 or does it renew 30 days after?
habituss: Hey, just arrived, what he is working on ?
papouillette: 30d after
Joooooooooonas: @EhGuyInCanada 30 days
gigafact: who cares just do it
EhGuyInCanada: hmmm okay im thinking about it
papouillette: a 1000 subs there will be viewer games
gigafact: it cost you nothing and you still think about it. you already paid for it lol
bitabuse_: Which colorscheme of vim is he using?
JediPotatoPotato: @EhGuyInCanada you have to manually renew prime every month if you sub that way.
blaaaaz3: I can't believe I find entertaining watching a guy writing things that I dont undestand CoolStoryBob
Joooooooooonas: @gigafact maybe he wants to subsricbe someone else
gigafact: George is the only one
mashafique: Geo simps LUL
EhGuyInCanada: @JediPotatoPotato wdym? im pretty sure i have an annual amazon prime subscription so i shouldnt have to renew it for twitch
papouillette: do you think twitch can make a program? like twitch plays pokemon
TJSparks: I think there is one
EhGuyInCanada: and yeah i might want to subscribe to someone else so im not sure
gigafact: did you guys see any other streams. Do they make you do homework and take tests? no so subscribe to George for more tests!
Vanishyi: is this the kind of question that would get me banned?
EhGuyInCanada: if george lets us take a makeuo test then i will subscribe
TheKoreanZombi: who else would you want to subscribe to? we will let you know if it makes sense over George.
notice_me_OpieOP: RonSmug
JediPotatoPotato: @EhGuyInCanada ugh, I'm saying if you give a streamer like geo your twitch prime sub, it only lasts a month and does not autorenew. If you want to give it to him for the second month you manually do it. vs a normal twitch sub which renews automatically. You also can google how twitch prime subs work
TheAbdullahAmrSobh: Hey George what are you coding?
EhGuyInCanada: @JediPotatoPotato oh okay gotcha
EhGuyInCanada: @TheKoreanZombi idk, maybe GMNaroditsky or Hikaru
notice_me_OpieOP: @TheAbdullahAmrSobh https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Busy_beaver
JediPotatoPotato: @TheAbdullahAmrSobh it's literally in the title homie
Poohcan: hi marge
gigafact: impressive progress keep going
TheAbdullahAmrSobh: haha sry didnt know what busy beaver is
gigafact: @TheAbdullahAmrSobh it's just beavers being busy
bubblesnot: @georgehotz if you solve it can i put my name on your paper too?
Foreigner369: hes writing busy beavers
n0_0xygen: what r u doing?
gigafact: anything what should be banned
papouillette: twitch chat in bibtex ofc
Nafferza: @bubblesnot add my name too thx
bubblesnot: I was here
Nakelsmith: LOOK at this Handsome AND smart Guy wrote in his pc like a madman!!!
bradyry773: you write like donald trump
racksoup_XD: What does the -pthread compiler flag do?
Foreigner369: :)
Pilot_Boudica: geo hot rocks
habituss: isn't it for multithreading @racksoup_XD
homebr3w: TPFufun
EhGuyInCanada: okay should i subscribe?
the_g_aka_the_baap: WAYTOODANK
EhGuyInCanada: i think im going to do it
gigafact: @EhGuyInCanada go ahead
JdPaulBlart: O(N^epic)
bubblesnot: Do it
racksoup_XD: @habituss I know what pthread is, but I don't know what the flag does.
JediPotatoPotato: And here I am feeling proud of myself for getting through college Algebra
visheshsinha: POSIX Threads, usually referred to as pthreads, is an execution model that exists independently from a language, as well as a parallel execution model. It allows a program to control multiple different flows of work that overlap in time.
EhGuyInCanada: alright its free anyway
EhGuyInCanada: EhGuyInCanada subscribed with Twitch Prime.
habituss: "-pthread Adds support for multithreading with the pthreads library. This option sets flags for both the preprocessor and linker." @racksoup_XD
trump4200000: George Hotz 2020
Poohcan: you should be proud @JediPotatoPotato, that's pretty good for a potato
gigafact: well done @EhGuyInCanada
JediPotatoPotato: heh pooh
trump4200000: PartyTime
bubblesnot: @ehguyincanada you just fed a homeless George for a week
EhGuyInCanada: yeet
gigafact: you even got a shutout it's rare
TJSparks: wow giving money to rich people :/
TJSparks: instead give it to me
trump4200000: my bad
EhGuyInCanada: wait why dont I have a star beside my name?
mashafique: elaGa chat
TJSparks: you do
EhGuyInCanada: oh wait now I do nvm
gigafact: you have it now
bubblesnot: @tjsparks you are the problem
trump4200000: PartyTime
JediPotatoPotato: @TJSparks lol I mean do you accept twitch primes?
Lefer_: Imagine subbing and not even getting emotes LUL
racksoup_XD: I didn't know you needed a flag. I thought it could just be included.
trump4200000: i need a drink
JdPaulBlart: https://networthroom.com/blog/george-hotz-net-worth-bio/
gigafact: we need another hype train. how do you summon the hype train?
trump4200000: George is ignoring us
aj37z: need to use arrow function
gigafact: @trump4200000 he is focoued
TJSparks: wait he doesn't have any emotes?
mosin_lol: what is the goal in that ? some 1 explain^^
Joooooooooonas: @gigafact random , can happen if someone subs or uses bits
habituss: it says george is worth $25m lol
gigafact: @Joooooooooonas interesting
bradyry773: mosin_lol: hes hacking the beavers mainframe
the_EZPZ: Did george test the chatters if they read the paper?
ravicat: @mosin_lol the challenge
EhGuyInCanada: yes @the_EZPZ
ravicat: @EhGuyInCanada how so?
bradyry773: yeahhhh
JediPotatoPotato: I have not read the paper... haHAA
a1eaiactaest: hello everyone
gigafact: @the_EZPZ https://forms.gle/2QiYgde4aMkFY9DKA
EhGuyInCanada: he gave a test at the beginning of the stream
bubblesnot: , ai is worth 5b+ in twitch primes
trump4200000: PartyTime
nixon36: 469% cpu
habituss: @the_EZPZ Can you the link to the paper ?
Joooooooooonas: @habituss maybe his company but its loan salary is around 5-6k, said it on stream
bradyry773: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
theVooTy: I wish I could focus like him
world2vec: geohot is in his flow
habituss: ty @bradyry773
JediPotatoPotato: @theVooTy you have two choices. Autism or aderall
trump4200000: PartyTime
visheshsinha: LUL
bradyry773: here's hoping i make it to youtube
Lefer_: LUL
TJSparks: good work i guess
bubblesnot: @jdpaulblart LOL
gigafact: George we need to test emote only chat
ravicat: @gigafact wait is it IQ test XD
JdPaulBlart: can you show the responses to that google form
trump4200000: I need a new gun and all the shops are understocked
bitabuse_: Which vim color scheme is he using?
trump4200000: PartyTime
Joooooooooonas: Are we faster now with threads ?
gigafact: what was that
Lefer_: SWAT? monkaS
kingvoneduard: The police
JohnnyThe_Hobo: they are coming monkaS
JediPotatoPotato: What google form?
trump4200000: pizzas here
fyfo321: monkaS
Bretel: beeeeeeen xD
gigafact: Scam is here
trump4200000: go get you're sandwich XD
kingvoneduard: Feds come after you
world2vec: fbi open the door
thetimetraveler253: no Makefile NotLikeThis
trump4200000: it's Jeff bezos
kingvoneduard: Fedex guy with a gun
trump4200000: PartyTime
gigafact: who?
virgilvs: sorry I'm out of the loop, what have you been up to these past few years?
raad1masum: whats in the drink
bradyry773: elon at the door
trump4200000: coconut water
joaovictorsnt: fbi
TJSparks: every 5 mins
trump4200000: George FaceTime elon musk
trump4200000: PartyTime
bradyry773: yesss
habituss: @virgilvs he became an instagram influencer
bradyry773: looks sweet
Joooooooooonas: Are we faster now with threads ? @georgehotz
gigafact: some people actually got raided on stream
thetimetraveler253: CPU getting a workout today
EhGuyInCanada: cant ddos a hacker
trump4200000: monkaS
kingvoneduard: Secret Service: The President needs you Aliens are here!
TJSparks: put that apple cpu to work
bradyry773: how long do you need this tor run?
trump4200000: no longer in the shadows
gigafact: this is fast
TowlieGotHigh: ResidentSleeper
virgilvs: @habituss glad he made it
32bitrobo: what are you doin
JediPotatoPotato: So the goal is to beat the longest running record right?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: D:
raad1masum: kaboom
Poohcan: low quality chat today
trump4200000: Pentagon just discovered aliens
im_bat_boy: Nice Shoot
gigafact: George are you going to halt?
JediPotatoPotato: halts as soon as he stands up heh
trump4200000: that was a serious gamer move
bradyry773: how long will it run for?
Slybluedemon: What is this for?
Elinbae: why not beat it?
trump4200000: PartyTime
mashafique: @Poohcan Provide something high quality. Go. elaGa
Elinbae: that is not a productive and winning mentality
Joooooooooonas: Didnt there was one code running on a german supercomputer ?
bradyry773: Ice tea time G
thetimetraveler253: George were you impressed by Elon Musk
Lefer_: @Poohcan how large percentage of chat has an idea what George is doing do you think LUL
im_bat_boy: Listen to beat it by lil peep Kappa
TJSparks: you didn't reset i think
trump4200000: THROW IT HARDER
visheshsinha: PogChamp
joaovictorsnt: lol
world2vec: I dont even know what he's coding, the wiki article and pdf are moonspeak to me ;_;
trump4200000: PartyTime
JohnnyThe_Hobo: so many things
TJSparks: lol
JediPotatoPotato: download more
gigafact: rip swap
DasMastah: Offload to disk?
EhGuyInCanada: @Lefer_ according to the quiz results, only like 6 people actually understand what he is doing
PutYourMoneyOnMe: download more ram
Bretel: ahahah
JohnnyThe_Hobo: you can always download mode ram
ManiacBlack: LUL
TowlieGotHigh: MAC KEKW
trump4200000: George Floyd George Hotz George Soros
thetimetraveler253: quick get a AWS instance and do rsync
Lefer_: @EhGuyInCanada And Im not among those 6 LUL
bradyry773: aint nothing wrong with swab
BernardoFire: macbook sucks haha
trump4200000: TheIlluminati
itzahmerob: LOL
kingvoneduard: George is cracking Twitter code again
Pilot_Boudica: listen to that cooling fan trying to take off
gigafact: make it run on bad hardware
itzahmerob: Ban that guy pls
EhGuyInCanada: politics bad
bubblesnot: But can you prove the record in 20lines or less?
trump4200000: mmmkay
gigafact: optimize optimize optimize
TJSparks: YES!
JediPotatoPotato: AWS here we come
Joooooooooonas: here we go bois
thetimetraveler253: oh snap
fyfo321: memory leak bois
im_bat_boy: Run it on a amazon cloud . don't be parsimonious
thetimetraveler253: George getting into the Ferrari
bradyry773: this is it
uint32t: 499 packages can be updated
martinoestuessy: obs is not enjoying this load lol
kingvoneduard: Buy some RAM with Bitcoin from Twitter
bubblesnot: I was here
trump4200000: PartyTime
gigafact: damn
bradyry773: my body is ready
JediPotatoPotato: lets do it
nixon36: holy
TJSparks: wtf
JohnnyThe_Hobo: lets freaking gooooo
world2vec: let's go
heyitsrama: lmao
itzahmerob: the POWA
32bitrobo: jiga bhytes
SolarBerry: big jigs
habituss: wat that 250 ?
thetimetraveler253: did he just download more ram
world2vec: jfc
JediPotatoPotato: all of the jigga bites
JohnnyThe_Hobo: he downloaded ALL THE RAM
YouPowerRush: HahaReindeer
Pilot_Boudica: gigga jigga bytesies
gigafact: time to heat up the office
bradyry773: TEN THOUSAND JIGAWATTS
trump4200000: PartyTime
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz another q&a at the end of the stream?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: lets freaking gooo
visheshsinha: Donload RAMS LUL LUL
world2vec: now george is cooking with oil
jotembruv: wow with that many gidjabytes you can hack nasa
jisaku: are you still on 8 threads
bradyry773: eyyy
trump4200000: I just made some RAM pasta
JohnnyThe_Hobo: why the stopies?
bradyry773: big brain time
Mayfieldiv: poor core 25
im_bat_boy: You gotta install arch linux . it's faster Kappa
Elinbae: this is why you should use linux
Elinbae: linux doesnt use ram
DasMastah: More cores
solitaryyy: should have written it in golang
Joooooooooonas: what computer are u using now ? workcomputer ?
thetimetraveler253: one core sweating hard while rest chilling
JediPotatoPotato: What's the record?
Nafferza: Where is the I have no idea what is going on (brick) emoji
Mayfieldiv: good one george
Pilot_Boudica: hahaha coding humor
PutYourMoneyOnMe: do you allocate anything? some shitty malloc stuff can freeze
bradyry773: woww
TJSparks: Kreygasm OMG
SolarBerry: lmfao
JohnnyThe_Hobo: D:
visheshsinha: Nicee
prawins: OMG
TowlieGotHigh: Kreygasm
trump4200000: PartyTime
iilliilliillli: ll
visheshsinha: Kreygasm Kreygasm
blaaaaz3: what a nice political simbol
nico_d0t: Kreygasm
SolarBerry: nooo bring it back
aj37z: Coomer
gigafact: good mod
iiiiiiillllliiiill: @iilliilliillli HeyGuys
rustduck: DansGame i was cooming
iilliilliillli: monkaS iiiiiiillllliiiill
Pilot_Boudica: middle out compression?
theVooTy: MercyWing1 PixelBob
JediPotatoPotato: inb4 200mil
JdPaulBlart: cool numbers bro
TJSparks: @iiiiiiillllliiiill @iilliilliillli monkaS
TowlieGotHigh: Busy beaver is going strong monkaS
bradyry773: i think 300
DasMastah: Are you excluding 0-dextrous?
Joooooooooonas: what computer are u using now ? workcomputer ? @georgehotz
jotembruv: make the letters green and it looks like a scene from a movie
bubblesnot: See if Bezos has something faster you can use
JediPotatoPotato: @georgehotz is the goal to beat the record?
virgilvs: so did you end up building that self-driving car
trump4200000: Amazon RAM
JohnnyThe_Hobo: yeah... we've all been there
brickeyy: monkaS
itzahmerob: many millions
JohnnyThe_Hobo: but what do the numbers mean
smurfd0: 6 states wil have more gillions
kingvoneduard: If George crack the Matrix code we are f@ed
TowlieGotHigh: So u made us do 1/2 of a test on a paper that u don't like anymore YEP
TJSparks: wow stop leaking my money in my bank account
world2vec: lmao 10 hours later: I don't like this paper
Knarez: yeah ik it doesnt matter but
bradyry773: nahhh
Mayfieldiv: for fast single-threaded server performance, we've used OVH gaming servers
JediPotatoPotato: He's doing 5 states, right?
bradyry773: it frize
Knarez: when and why did he go to screen from tmux lol
PutYourMoneyOnMe: attach gdb when it freezes
trump4200000: PartyTime
Joooooooooonas: LUL
bradyry773: 300 here we come
Joooooooooonas: 70gigs nice uff
virgilvs: Any plans on becoming a billionaire?
Knarez: oh hes on a server i see
fishpizza: 21 hours LUL
habituss: What do you think about Rust @georgehotz ?
mattdacentaur: KappaHD
bradyry773: come on 300
trump4200000: PartyTime
caster64o: WOOO NUMBER GO DOWN
visheshsinha: Yeah
solitaryyy: You would probably have better perf if you didn't print so much
bubblesnot: Are we about to break sha2
JohnnyThe_Hobo: catching the beaver PogChamp
Mayfieldiv: we're goin' down, down
Joooooooooonas: do we get it before 250gigs of ram
visheshsinha: PogChamp PogChamp
bradyry773: haha
brickeyy: smaller
raad1masum: smaller
gigafact: smaller
jisaku: larger
ced0xF: smaller
pxlluu: larger
ravicat: larger
bojosos: smaller 2k bits
fishpizza: larger
JediPotatoPotato: larger heh
norflin221: >
prawins: smaller
Pilot_Boudica: pre or post covid?
forgnath: ==
itzahmerob: >
bradyry773: uh oh
brickeyy: 2
pxlluu: 328m
habituss: 350
UniqumTV: 340M~
ManiacBlack: 338 mil
fishpizza: 330 mil
trump4200000: I'm betting 50,000$
tjbrother: Same
smurfd0: moar than us
bradyry773: come on 300
Joooooooooonas: the ram is gonna be a close one
EhGuyInCanada: @pxlluu nice speed there
thetimetraveler253: it'll be 470M
habituss: if it goes over, you get my prime
CJslider14: the programmers wheel of fortune
sonerbliznakov: Can someone explain me what is happening at the right side with all these codes?
Vjasal: monkaS it's dead
jotembruv: F
bradyry773: it frozeee....
world2vec: dead
prawins: Is it dead ?\
TJSparks: lol
DasMastah: You should serialize the results
trump4200000: XDXDXD
gigafact: moar
ravicat: @sonerbliznakov new machines and computing them
JediPotatoPotato: @georgehotz I think you might need to disable your popup blocker, I think that'll fix it.
fishpizza: monkaS more...
thetimetraveler253: 90G/225G used Kreygasm
aj37z: its taking over PC MrDestructoid
JohnnyThe_Hobo: when i grow up i want to be george...
PutYourMoneyOnMe: should be able to switch to some nicer allocator
iiiiiiillllliiiill: why is he not folding proteins anymore, he was our biggest hope against covid
bradyry773: ooooo
GerbilJay: @georgehotz can i ask you 2 questions?
bubblesnot: I think 69million
thetimetraveler253: George how big is your USB stick
ravicat: @georgehotz so how long did it take as of now?
kingvoneduard: Huuuuuuuuuuge
aj37z: MrDestructoid im conscious
foti_kasparov: VoteYea VoteYea
stickyshrimp: what is this
bradyry773: nahhhh
Joooooooooonas: we are getting slower
notice_me_OpieOP: wtf MrDestructoid
bradyry773: >300
gigafact: you can't change
prawins: I told yah
TowlieGotHigh: 64 thread CPU, using only 1 thread PepeLaugh
visheshsinha: PeoplesChamp
trump4200000: PartyTime
stickyshrimp: crash the stream
smurfd0: betting both over and under?
trump4200000: threehunnid
gigafact: lol
itzahmerob: can't change LUL
3johnsonn3: LUL
Lefer_: LUL
gigafact: core15 hamster7 working hard
ManiacBlack: core 15 just chuggin along
norlagg: what kind of mac is he using
Joooooooooonas: Just like group work LUL
lightofhel1: what's the cpu is?
iilliilliillli: what cpu is that, epyc?
YouPowerRush: so brave
trump4200000: PartyTime
EhGuyInCanada: YES
damini0s: Under 300?
Pilot_Boudica: You dating yet?
self__repr__: naw
notice_me_OpieOP: PartyTime
Vjasal: VIP only QnA
norflin221: no subscribers only
jisaku: carrier pigeon only q&a
EhGuyInCanada: subscribers only q&a sounds good
foti_kasparov: Make a theme this time
smurfd0: https://github.com/pkrumins/busy-beaver . that one has a working cpp and py beaver
ravicat: LUL we did not do good last time, maybe you are better off LUL
notice_me_OpieOP: me Kappa /
Poohcan: george only q&a
fishpizza: 21 hours
TheKoreanZombi: Yes, subscribers only
im_bat_boy: No subscribers only . Let us talk boyyy
JohnnyThe_Hobo: 24 hours stream PogChamp
pxlluu: @iilliilliillli intel® Xeon® Processor E5-2695 v4
TJSparks: what did they write in lol
Pilot_Boudica: those researchers are noobz
martinoestuessy: eyy
32bitrobo: hahahahah
thetimetraveler253: can you explain Turing Machine
bojosos: @georgehotz Did you compile with -O2
bubblesnot: I was here
GerbilJay: @georgehotz Q&A: your opinion on the UFO pentagon stuff?
martinoestuessy: 24 stream :O yess
itzahmerob: lolz
itzahmerob: nubs
trump4200000: SCAM
Coshbuc: they run it on a 8GB of RAM
gigafact: is it high performance if it runs slow on intel pentium 4?
JediPotatoPotato: Wasn't the original busy beaver theorized in the 60s?
norflin221: not subscribers only qa
jotembruv: CPP BABYYY
eldac_kno: what are your thoughts on Data Oriented game engines?
notice_me_OpieOP: V1 ZULUL
bradyry773: witnessing beaver history
Lefer_: LUL
GerbilJay: LOL!
french_salad: LUL
danyalej: Thoughts on new apple silicon?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: LUL
EhGuyInCanada: OHHHHHH got em
39BiggusDikus: but im not a subscriber
ravicat: LUL
atom9006: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
GerbilJay: @georgehotz LOL! love it
xaxxjs: lol
bradyry773: 300 is close!
JediPotatoPotato: LUL
gigafact: go go go
TheLogg: lol
notice_me_OpieOP: D:
young_beans_and_lean: busy beaver unsafe, rewrite in rust
foti_kasparov: Will it pass the number of neurons of dog?
Pilot_Boudica: mega gigga bitez
itzahmerob: 2.52 JIGGAWATS
Joooooooooonas: dont you want to get it to work on multithreaded, i mean that are many cores you could use
im_bat_boy: Q&A about Life
world2vec: 252 gb ram, goddamn
bradyry773: beaver history
jisaku: it isn't doing nothing, you are running chrome
bubblesnot: I think some of the best questions come from non subscribers
TowlieGotHigh: BAN HIM, He is ruining my CPs for QnA FeelsBadMan
fishpizza: LUL
thetimetraveler253: why is the RAM usage going up? what are we storing in memory
jisaku: just open some tabs and it will fill up all of that ram
trump4200000: PartyTime
Pilot_Boudica: pauses = puter taking bio breaks
damini0s: Pause for comercial LUL
tjbrother: What’s hammer?
CJslider14: do you think we can get below 0.4nm silicon transistors?
jagger_rsw: is it the most common pronounciation of GB in US - jiga?
Vjasal: rip ssd
Boonight2: are you jailbreaking the ps5 Kappa
gigafact: are you sure you code is optimized?
ravicat: @thetimetraveler253 turing machines
world2vec: you can run slack and two tabs on google chrome with all that ram
Tapeda: What do you think of the symbolic language ala wolfram approach to information I/O
itzahmerob: LOL
jotembruv: nobody says jiga its a meme
Pilot_Boudica: hammer industries
ravicat: @thetimetraveler253 and their calculations
bradyry773: just like ready player one
PeinlicherAffe: our servers are better Kappa
BernardoFire: sounds like a good plan
stickyshrimp: kill me
bojosos: @georgehotz Did you compile with -O2
eldac_kno: thoughts on Data Oriented programming for video games? Do you think it's justified? Or it's better to focus on rendering?
im_bat_boy: is it hammer.ai ?
bradyry773: come on 300 my baby
trump4200000: uhhh
gigafact: bye bye ram
b4b00nb0y: Top 5 recommended programming languages? And when are you going to make a book?
thetimetraveler253: George puckering up
Pencode: ye but can it run crysis 3 ?
Mayfieldiv: I'm glad you stopped running it on your MBP. would've run out of disk space
notice_me_OpieOP: any VCs in chat? 😎
PeinlicherAffe: @b4b00nb0y no
orseti_: this guy just said jigabytes smh
TJSparks: yea they double. And they don't resize
bradyry773: poor thing cant handle
kingvoneduard: I will make a company Sickle
PutYourMoneyOnMe: do a "watch free -h" in another term
divamgupta: lol design an ASIC to emulate your turing machine .... wait i already have one.
JediPotatoPotato: what else is this server running heh
world2vec: what's filling up all that ram?
solitarynative: vcs are dumb
bubblesnot: Can you add ssl to hammer.lol?
thetimetraveler253: George let's play some beats and do a freestyle
32bitrobo: where did you learn to code?
foti_kasparov: CORE DUMPED
stickyshrimp: ok dude sure
eldac_kno: even switch can run Crysis at 30 fps
trump4200000: PartyTime
TJSparks: lol
gamerguy009: Thoughts on neuralink
benjamindover146: They dont always double. Usually, they have some sort of smart resizing algorithm
TJSparks: I CANT SEE
bradyry773: damnnnn
notice_me_OpieOP: chu mean real MrDestructoid
bradyry773: whats the number?
fishpizza: TTours
TJSparks: WHAT NUMBER LOL
bradyry773: ooooo
bradyry773: i was close
Pilot_Boudica: not gonna have trouble fapping to this code
gigafact: its lower
b4b00nb0y: Thoughts on learning c first?
trump4200000: bay area Q&A only
stickyshrimp: you won
bluespeck: I think they double on reallocations... but you can reserve the memory from the beginning if you have an idea of the size it would get.
JohnnyThe_Hobo: so many machineeees
stickyshrimp: Clap
Pencode: LUL
PeinlicherAffe: F
Knarez: LUL
itzahmerob: W
JohnnyThe_Hobo: lets freaking goooooo
young_beans_and_lean: EZ PZY
trump4200000: PartyTime
benjamindover146: Use std::vector::reserve and std::vector::emplace_back. also, always pass by reference
thetimetraveler253: F
hjklhjklhjkl2008: the halting machine is solvable assuming the universe is finite and heat death is inevitable LUL
Luke9978: Better thread that baby
trump4200000: do it
kingvoneduard: You need more RAM
young_beans_and_lean: dedicated wam
orseti_: @georgehotz thoughts on the epstein & ghislane maxwell stuff
thetimetraveler253: eorge let's play some beats and do a freestyle
foti_kasparov: 1GB TXT FILE HOLDING THE NUMBER
Mayfieldiv: 0-dextrous feels unappreciated
Pilot_Boudica: I'm an old lady (really) who just started coding python...can I have a job with your company? <3
theduckthough: hi, what's george doing? :)
bradyry773: https://arxiv.org/pdf/1610.03184.pdf
habituss: habituss subscribed with Twitch Prime.
PeinlicherAffe: y doe
EhGuyInCanada: can we use that website for the q&a again?
Pilot_Boudica: Pilot_Boudica subscribed at Tier 1.
TJSparks: imagine subbing LUL
bubblesnot: Welcome to the inner circle boys
trump4200000: :0
trump4200000: PartyTime
gigafact: how does it feel to be an amazon employee? Twitch is owned by amazon
Pilot_Boudica: shit, now you know I'm a grill
Mayfieldiv: new ways to lose VIP?
Dautlog: More tests PogChamp
TriXav1er: are questions only about busy beaver?
norlagg: LUL
ravicat: I did not subscribe and still can write LUL
TowlieGotHigh: When will you start using a 2nd monitor so u don't have to alt tab to look at twitch chat? monkaHmm
notice_me_OpieOP: that's messed up cmon bruh RonSmug
topbxy: -430 points TriHard
ngh7mr3: still bypassed, nice mode
solitarynative: -430
eldac_kno: Thoughts on Data-Oriented programming for video games? Do you think it's better to focus on rendering?
EhGuyInCanada: when will the makeup test be?
world2vec: -430 lmao
fizziblytwitching: What spec is the Xeon?
1v3ease: nice
Pilot_Boudica: How do I get VIP?
SHAVEYY_: vip people can spam PogChamp
instagrab: snip snap snip snap
solitaryyy: What happens when we hit the 100 VIP limit?
Pilot_Boudica: oh wow
Waldoqq: THE SYSTEM IS RIGGED!!!
EhGuyInCanada: when will the makeup test be??
yellowolf23: -5$ TriHard
Pilot_Boudica: where are the tests?
trump4200000: PartyTime
tjbrother: Code merge sort on stream? LUL
ced0xF: if you could run one program on a turing machine with an oracle what would it be?
ced0xF: yes one bit
PeinlicherAffe: don't you have more than 250gb RAM for your calculations?
JediPotatoPotato: @georgehotz what's your next business venture?
EhGuyInCanada: have you solved p=np yet?
Pilot_Boudica: Have you considered using quantum tunneling (quantum eraser) to send data back in time (this actually works), and trade the stock market?
bubblesnot: Could commas ai cameras be used to decentralize police officers body cam footage?
krystalgamer: if your instagram blows up would you consider moving these streams to that amazing platform?
gigafact: Are you going to do a chat bot with https://dev.twitch.tv/docs/api/ ?
Pilot_Boudica: not far, just a few seconds
EhGuyInCanada: when will the makeup test be?
eldac_kno: Shouldn't it be is Goldbach conjecture provable?
Pilot_Boudica: You can, I've managed to get a few ms back.
Pilot_Boudica: but I'm not a hf trader
CJslider14: Do you think we will be able to go smaller than 0.6nm silicon transistors? you would need at least 1 atom/ terminal i'm assuming(@ .2nm/atm)
instagrab: Have you ever considered teaching reverse engineering?
bojosos: What happened to Alex?
SHAVEYY_: would you be interested in making an IRC server for the stream?
smurfd0: did you use the _mini or _full local dump of wikipedia?
Joooooooooonas: Dont you want to add Sub-Icons /Emotes , BTTV , Nightbot etc
ThePepe3012: Why are you in nyc?
jordandiaz1988: How do you stay pampered when you program or read?
39BiggusDikus: is this live
EhGuyInCanada: when will the makeup test be??
notice_me_OpieOP: I'll consider subscribing if you add PepeLaugh
Pilot_Boudica: where are the tests?
Vektorraum: it might be provable but constructing the proof might not be possible in our universe
jordandiaz1988: How do you stay pampered when you program or read??
GerbilJay: your opinion on the best way to increase personal intelligence? how to get smarter.
trump4200000: :0
SHAVEYY_: how many times have you failed a captcha :)
Pilot_Boudica: I am a fan girl
lemonsauc3: What is one of your favourite books? Just asking since I saw the kindle app.
BernardoFire: @georgehotz can the next test be algorithms and DS ? please
itzahmerob: itzahmerob subscribed at Tier 1.
EhGuyInCanada: what's your IQ?
eldac_kno: Do you think common answer about "Infinite Sum" to Zeno's Dichotomy is not a good answer?
bubblesnot: How hard is it to build/manufacture and sell hardware?
gigafact: Will you check some hammer comments on https://www.youtube.com/post/UgwXAIOEMtXU3IJ1mOt4AaABCQ
solitaryyy: "Hammer it"
nico_d0t: You can always go smaller and smaller the issue is interference. Research should be going into attenuating that interference
PeinlicherAffe: how did you get your local wikipedia and does it contain every article?
liej6799: lol
pxlluu: read the paper but could not understand a few things. Your streams are great so far
world2vec: 360usd per year is a lot
djceci: Are we sure alexa is not eavesdropping again?
BernardoFire: CEOs use superhuman, they can pay a lot. Hammer should be for "everyone". right?
SHAVEYY_: cmonBruh
gigafact: rip hammer
trump4200000: TURN OFF ALEXA
EhGuyInCanada: what's your IQ??
Pilot_Boudica: I love to take people for a drive in my car and pretend to fall asleep. When they ask who's driving, I say "Geo is driving!"
CJslider14: the SIMP Engine
nanodanger7: still playing chess?
notice_me_OpieOP: cmonBruh
chemicalflash: Regarding the IQ improvement on Dogs question from yesterday, how would you do it on twitch non-subs ?
instagrab: Have you ever considered teaching reverse engineering for a premium?
bojosos: Do something for sub announcement similar to what Michael Reeves did with a drill
eldac_kno: I didn't think you are prescriptivist kinda guy, You always gave an impression of descriptivist in the field of linguistics
the_EZPZ: Top 10 ways to be a smart human and good programmer PogChamp
gigafact: VIP gets to play chess with George ?
solitaryyy: "10 Facts You Didn't Know About Geohot!"
Santiago_LHC: 10 Ways In Which Hammer Will Change The World
martinoestuessy: ey georgie are you scared of gpt-3 too?
TheOnlyJoric: 13 ways hammer will change your life
benjamindover146: I wrote a web scraper to download all of wikipedia. It indexed like 300 wikipedia subdomains and like a thousand other websites. It was all great until I found out wikiprdia allows you to download all their articles through a download link. Mega F
TriXav1er: @georgehotz is there a good resource for localization or should I just look at google papers?
Mayfieldiv: when are you heading back to SD?
Pilot_Boudica: \o/ everyone gets a hammer
martinkirilov: I want a sword, not a hammer Kappa
itzahmerob: ty for hammer George
solitaryyy: He's gota get laid in NYC
bubblesnot: @benjamindover146 haha
tjbrother: Do you think 10x better search is possible without reindexing everything?
brickeyy: should i go to college @georgehotz
blueberryguac: are you in dirty jersey
EhGuyInCanada: @georgehotz what are the two best fields to study in college, in your opinion?
Pilot_Boudica: You wanna take my sailboat and go travel?
itzahmerob: How's the company going?
eldac_kno: How would answer Zeno Dichotomy? About half of the half of the way
smurfd0: suprised you didnt have "hammer time" as a video on the hammer page :P
jagger_rsw: george goes to iceland to be tested for covid
Pilot_Boudica: 33
trump4200000: PartyTime
ThePepe3012: Do you think that data protection laws in europe are a right approach?
Pilot_Boudica: 33ft benetau
32bitrobo: how smart is Lex Fridman?
gigafact: is it possible to reverse aging?
chemicalflash: what places you visit in Iceland ?
TheOnlyJoric: who's your smash main bro
Vektorraum: are you familiar with CFSG and its relation to the graph isomorphism problem? might be useful for this problem
trump4200000: i already do that?
RAMBOxBEAST: Favorite place to travel?
Pilot_Boudica: it's got an autopilot and you can sail it from your ipad in bed
EhGuyInCanada: easy
itzahmerob: Whew Smash64
trump4200000: bet 5000K
5GToren: sup trump
trump4200000: @5gtoren zup
jagger_rsw: amiga or atari?
EhGuyInCanada: @jordandiaz1988 are you trying to get muted?
Pilot_Boudica: Dude, if you wanna do it, I'm up for it. It's got 2 sleeper cabins...shower room, kitchen, main cabin, etc...
gigafact: nice stream. thanks for being you.
bubblesnot: Could we do a ctf for one of the upcoming streams?
bojosos: What happened to Alex?
lesserthangood: i love big butts and i cannot lie
Pilot_Boudica: nice, well let me know
turmoffstream: bye
eldac_kno: thoughts on Zeno's Dichotomy? Why people think "Infinite Sum" answer is a good answer to it?
CJslider14: is the stream chat testing considered a high pass filter for the noise
itzahmerob: Makeup test tomorrow?
Pilot_Boudica: it's in maryland
myaocat: Making a key concepts from book/article using NLP. How hard is it to make a good one? (thanks :3)
trump4200000: PartyTime
Mayfieldiv: ooo a CTF would be fun
PeinlicherAffe: your questions were really easy btw (if you know something about logic and busy beaver)
3rdeyer: Good stream!
BernardoFire: bye
EhGuyInCanada: :(
phrixus_bro: bye
gigafact: bye
hey_is_me987: Good stream now I need to get back to work
gigafact: that bye was so soft
BernardoFire: is he gonna stream tommmorrow??
georgehotz: lol PeinlicherAffe where's your VIP?
trump4200000: yes it is
YouPowerRush: beey
bubblesnot: Pico ctf is great
Aldoassassin: lova you man
Nafferza: NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
trump4200000: PartyTime
myaocat: damn on my question. BibleThump
ConagYuirg: bye
bluespeck: first programming language you liked?